<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tripfinder>
  <destinationpages>
    
    <destinations category="casinos" reg="allinclusive">
        <row locid="10341" lat="39.384664" long="-74.500476">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Atlantic City</location>
            <state>New Jersey</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Vegas-like casinos]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[For those searching for a Vegas experience closer to the East Coast, Atlantic City on the Jersey Shore comes up a winner. Whether you're looking for an exclusive casino or a gaming palace done up in a wild west theme, you'll find it here. If you're on a quest for nightlife, look no further than the city's thumpin' clubs. Then rise with the sun (if you went to sleep at all) and stroll the famous boardwalk while waves lap tranquil beaches.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_atlanticcity.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10341" lat="39.384664" long="-74.500476">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Biloxi</location>
            <state>Mississippi</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Vegas-like casinos]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mississippi Gulf Coast, one of America's most affordable vacation getaways, is where you'll discover vibrant Biloxi. Gaming fans flock to its casinos to try their hand at high limit tables and liberal house rules. Enjoy all the amenities high rollers have come to expect in the city's sumptuously appointed resort hotels. Spend your winnings dining and taking in top-notch entertainment. Biloxi's the place for gaming fun with a southern twist.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_atlanticcity.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10341" lat="39.384664" long="-74.500476">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Shreveport</location>
            <state>Louisiana</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Vegas-like casinos]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[It's all about gaming southern style in Shreveport, Louisiana. Climb aboard one of the city's five Red River riverboat casinos, where you'll enjoy state-of-the-art entertainment in a setting that evokes the glamour of the past. When you've had your fill at the tables, hop on over to catch some horse-racing at Louisiana Downs in nearby Bossier City. Need to unwind? Botanical gardens and fine dining beckon those looking for relaxation.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_atlanticcity.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10341" lat="39.384664" long="-74.500476">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Laughlin</location>
            <state>Nevada</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Vegas-like casinos]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Laughlin, Nevada, nestled on the banks of the Colorado River, attracts gaming enthusiasts with the affordable charms of eleven resort casinos. When you arrive, hop on a water shuttle to visit gaming houses tricked out with all the latest attractions. After you've cashed out your winnings, enjoy some superb recreation, including hiking beautiful Grapevine Canyon. Known as a great alternative to Vegas, Laughlin is blessed with natural splendor.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_atlanticcity.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="1068" lat="42.353768" long="-83.092130">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Detroit</location>
            <state>Michigan</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Casinos, Cars and Culture in the Motor City]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Detroit, famous for muscle cars and Motown, is increasingly known as the gaming enthusiast's destination of choice. Play the tables in any number of the city's superb hotel casinos, then check the exchange rate and hop over to the Canadian gaming hub of Windsor, Ontario, just a short trip away aboard the Ambassador Bride. When you're on a quest for great values in the Motor City, luck is on your side.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Detroit.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2008" lat="36.129911" long="-115.124986">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Las Vegas</location>
            <state>Nevada</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Over 122,000 slot machines.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Where can you enjoy world class food, shopping, shows, and gaming in hotels that make your jaw drop? It's Vegas, baby! Find out why Las Vegas delivers sensational entertainment to over 37 million visitors a year. Try your luck on nickel slots or go head to head with the high rollers. Kick back where Sinatra hung his hat or spot celebrities at the Strip's hottest clubs. Whatever your definition of a good time, Vegas provides it in spades.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_LasVegas.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2434" lat="29.970688" long="-90.052760">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>New Orleans</location>
            <state>Louisiana</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Harrah's Casino.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Sure, casinos around the world offer live entertainment, but when you're in New Orleans, some of the best music in the world is a block or two away. When you've had your fill of jazz, hit the tables at Harrah's, where you'll choose from 2,000 slot machines, 90 table games, and the largest poker room in the South. The Big Easy also offers riverboat gambling and the country's second oldest horse racing track at the New Orleans Fair Grounds.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_NewOrleans.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6025615" lat="18.257960" long="-65.665843">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Ceiba</location>
            <state>Puerto Rico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Rio Mar Beach Resort and Casino.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Where can you play Texas Hold 'Em within walking distance of a rainforest? Puerto Rico, that's where. With fifteen casinos dotting the island, this tropical oasis hosts the annual Caribbean Gaming Conference. Explore the island's jungles, tennis courts, championship golf courses, and fresh cuisine from the sea, all just a minute or two from some of the most gorgeous beaches on earth. Puerto Rico is where gaming enthusiasts stay to play.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_PuertoRico.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3018" lat="39.500357" long="-119.801604">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Reno</location>
            <state>Nevada</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Top rated big name casinos.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[A family-friendly escape with just as much glitter as Vegas, Reno makes memories. Maybe you'll remember striking it big at blackjack or at the roulette table, or just the perfect day at the spa. Those in search of sumptuous amenities in this gaming getaway will discover them at any number of top-rated casino hotels. In your time away from the tables, take in some of the region's mining town history or state-of-the-art entertainment.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Reno.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>South Lake Tahoe</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[From cabins to casinos, South Lake Tahoe offers sophistication amid rugged grandeur. Looking for a gaming experience that doesn't involve the glitz? Step up to the tables at any of Tahoe's  casino hotels and experience an elevated style of gaming. Then, winnings in hand, satiate your hunger at restaurants where celebrities enjoy the creations of celebrity chefs. Gaming equals good times in this ski-and-be-seen mountain getaway.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
            </row>
            <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Monte Carlo</region>
            <location>Monte Carlo</location>
            <state>Monte Carlo</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Monte Carlo is synonymous with wealth, opulence, glitz, and glamour. It's the wealthiest enclave of Monaco, which boasts the most expensive real estate on Earth. Dress to the nines and hit the Monte Carlo Casino, where you'll have a better-than-outside chance of spotting royalty or celebrities. While here, catch one of Monte Carlo's signature sporting events, including the F1 Monaco Grand Prix and the Monte Carlo Tennis Masters.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Bahamas</region>
            <location>Bahamas</location>
            <state>Bahamas</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[If the Bahaman sun should prove too bright, head for some indoor recreation in the country's fabled casinos. Play blackjack, craps, and roulette at Atlantis Paradise Island, a luxurious retreat with 90 table games and more than 1,000 slot machines. Then seek out the sports book at Crystal Palace Casino in Nassau, the area's largest casino and resort. Or strike it big in the Princess Casino, a 20,000 square foot Moorish-style gaming palace.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Aruba</region>
            <location>Aruba</location>
            <state>Aruba</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[A little-known fact: Aruba was the birthplace of Caribbean Stud Poker, which first appeared in 1988. The island is home to 11 casinos, many of which are open 24 hours. Try your luck in the Excelsior Casino's exclusive poker room. If you tire of the tables at the Hyatt Regency Casino, repair to the Copa Cabana Bar to savor a hand-rolled cigar. Or pull up a seat at one of the 32 gaming tables at Stellaris Casino, Aruba's largest.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Niagara Falls</region>
            <location>Niagara Falls</location>
            <state>Niagara Falls</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Niagara Falls is much more than just a series of mind-boggling waterfalls - it's also a casino-rich gaming destination. Explore the many casinos of neighboring Ontario, which has more casinos and gaming establishments than any other province in Canada. Or stay close to the Falls; three casinos are located adjacent to the area, and several casino hotels are located within steps of this natural wonder.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Calgary</region>
            <location>Calgary</location>
            <state>Calgary</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Calgary's reputation is steeped in cowboy traditions - saloons, country music, and the like. But casino gambling is becoming increasingly popular in this Alberta outpost. Play the odds at the Cash Casino, where 600 slot machines and 28 table games are ready to pay out. Or head to Casino Calgary, a massive, 52,000 square foot gaming space with 760 slots and 30 table games. Finally, the Deerfoot Inn Casino offers 680 slots and four restaurants.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Macau</region>
            <location>Macau</location>
            <state>Macau</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Macau's gambling reputation is second only to that of Las Vegas. This Chinese jurisdiction has become known as "the Monte Carlo of the Orient," and its name is well-earned. Choose among 28 casinos in the area, including the brand-new Wynn Macau, the MGM Grand Macau, and the Sands Macau. Whether you're a high roller - and there are plenty of them here - or a nickel slot fan, Macau's gorgeous casinos have a stool for you.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Lima</region>
            <location>Lima</location>
            <state>Lima</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Venture to the doorstep of the Inca Trail and experience the excitement of gaming in Peru. Lima's casinos are many, but begin with the Sheraton Hotel, which offers 40 gaming tables and 180 slots. Roll the dice at Marriott's Stellaris Hotel and Casino, where each guest room features an ocean view. Don't miss downtown's Los Delfines Hotel and Casino and its onsite "dolphinarium," which is home to a pair of resident dolphins.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Utrecht</region>
            <location>Utrecht</location>
            <state>Utrecht</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[The town of Utrecht, Netherlands has begun to carve out a niche as a luxury destination for gaming enthusiasts from across Europe. Should you tire of the four first-class casinos - including Casino Utrecht, with 83 table games and 1,040 slot machines - you can always explore the historical center of Utrecht, the de facto religious capital of Holland since the 700s. And you can always place a winning bet on the beauty of the Netherlands' countryside.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Baden-Baden</region>
            <location>Baden-Baden</location>
            <state>Baden-Baden</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Travel to one of Europe's oldest and grandest casinos in the German city of Baden-Baden. Casino Baden's 29 gaming tables and hundreds of slot machines are set in the Baden Kongresshaus, a grand Victorian building that was renovated in 2007. Play poker, blackjack, roulette, and other table games amongst a distinguished clientele - Casino Baden-Baden regularly attracts celebrities from Europe and beyond.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
            <region>Moscow</region>
            <location>Moscow</location>
            <state>Moscow</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Less neon and glitter.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Russia's recent economic growth has resulted in an impressive casino boom. Bring your black tie to the ritzy Casino Metropol, a gaming paradise near the Kremlin and Red Square. Come prepared - Metropol has a strict dress code and $25 minimums on its poker and roulette tables. Or venture 10 minutes from downtown to Hotel Orlyonok, Moscow's largest hotel/casino complex, which also has 15 restaurants, six bowling alleys, and a sprawling pool.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/casino/casino_Tahoe.png]]></image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="cities" reg="intl">
        <row locid="2114" lat="51.461648" long="-0.098855">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>London</location>
            <state>England</state>
            <site><![CDATA[100 historical theatres in London]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Europe's most populous city has a nightlife to match its size. Catch an unforgettable musical, show, or play at one of the city's 100 historical theaters, or discover the hottest visual art in the world at any of 200+ galleries. Crazy about museums? London has more than 300. And if you crave events - be they artistic, cultural, or sports - London has them, to the tune of 150 every day. New York may never sleep, but London never stands still.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_London.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2734" lat="48.851961" long="2.360312">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Paris</location>
            <state>France</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Centre Pompidou and the Rodin Museum]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[If Paris's museums, cafes, and monuments don't impress you, its shopping will. Expand your wardrobe in the world's fashion capital, and come home looking better than ever. Between shops, pay visits to Notre Dame de Paris, the Eiffel Tower, and the Arc de Triomphe - three of the most recognizable monuments on Earth. Oh, and those museums? They're some of the best in the world, too - especially the Louvre, Musee D'Orsay, and the Rodin Museum.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Paris.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="4278" lat="55.730201" long="12.570064">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Copenhagen</location>
            <state>Denmark</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Rosenborg Castle]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Copenhagen, the Scandinavian equivalent of Paris or London, is a booming metropolis that remains rooted in its history. Discover the many chambers and ballrooms of Rosenborg Castle, home to the Danish Royal Collections. Feel the presence of the Vikings at the Viking Ship Museum, where the remnants of legendary vessels are on display. Or scratch your shopping itch at the Stroget, a market that runs directly through the heart of this bustling city.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Copenhagen.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="179096" lat="41.901961" long="12.388971">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Rome</location>
            <state>Italy</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Rome is the capitol of Italy]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Italy's capital has seen its share of boom and bust - the city was founded in 753 BC. Immerse yourself in Rome's narrow streets, many of which are lined with sidewalk cafes, chic boutiques, and wine bars. Explore the towering nave of St. Peter's Basilica, located in Vatican City, a sovereign territory of the Catholic Church that is the world's smallest nation. And experience the majesty of the Coliseum, the Roman Empire's signature stadium.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Rome.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="181434" lat="-33.879865" long="151.216590">
            <region>Asia</region>
            <location>Sydney</location>
            <state>Australia</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Sydney Opera House]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[From Darling Harbour to Oxford Street, Sydney is alive with pubs, jazz haunts, and nightclubs. Stroll along Sydney Harbour and marvel at the stacked eggshell roof of the Sydney Opera House, the hub of the city's cultural activity. Spend the weekend perusing the nearby Rocks neighborhood, a historical district laden with boutiques, galleries, cafes, and a seasonal outdoor market. However you choose to kick back, Sydney gladly assists.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Sydney.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6005294" lat="43.658779" long="-79.399120">
            <region>North America</region>
            <location>Toronto</location>
            <state>Ontario</state>
            <site><![CDATA[CN Tower, Hockey Hall of Fame]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Toronto offers cultural activities and entertainment options galore. From Broadway shows in the Entertainment District to shopping at the expansive Eaton Centre, Toronto will never leave you at a loss for things to do. Explore the city's signature attractions, including the 1,825-foot CN Tower (the tallest structure in the Americas), the Hockey Hall of Fame, and the famous St. Lawrence Farmer's Market, founded in 1803.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Toronto.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="716" lat="-34.605957" long="-58.450235">
            <region>South America</region>
            <location>Buenos Aires</location>
            <state>Argentina</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Culture and Architecture (Gaudi)]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Often referred to as "the Paris of South America," Buenos Aires integrates European architecture and arts with the customs and traditions of Argentina and its Continental neighbors. Experience the glory of an opera in Teatro Colon, a world-famous opera house. Savor Argentina's steaks, wines, and coffees in the city's burgeoning dining scene, and finish your days with a tango at a nightclub - the dance, after all, was invented in Buenos Aires.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_BuenosAires.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2265" lat="19.396498" long="-99.150748">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Mexico City</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[The Historic Centre (Centro Historico)]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[From the dancers and musicians in El Zócalo to the floating gardens of Xochimilco, Mexico City teems with life, diversity, and art. Experience the baroque architecture of the Centro Historico, visit the Frida Kahlo Museum, and catch a live performance of the renowned National Symphony Orchestra at the Palacio de Bellas Artes. Finally, don't miss the Paseo de la Reforma, a stunning boulevard that was modeled after the Champs-Elysees.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_MexicoCity.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="4106" lat="49.248185" long="-123.146988">
            <region>North America</region>
            <location>Vancouver</location>
            <state>British Columbia</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Robson Street]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Vancouver sits at the junction of the civilized and natural worlds. Downtown, you'll find chic shops, excellent dining, and packed nightclubs on Robson Street. Yet a quick bus ride brings you to the forests and gardens of Stanley Park, a 1,000-acre urban oasis blessed with more than 500,000 trees. Then hop on a foot ferry to the public market and craft studios of Granville Island, or visit the Vancouver Art Museum, home to a 7,900-item collection.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Vancouver.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="4106" lat="49.248185" long="-123.146988">
            <region>South America</region>
            <location>Sao Paulo</location>
            <state>Sao Paulo</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Robson Street]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Strut your stuff - or watch others strut theirs - in Sao Paulo, the unofficial fashion capital of South America. (The city hosts one of the world's top Fashion Weeks, and supermodel Gisele Bundchen was discovered here.) Sample Sao Paulo's sophisticated cuisine, which ranges all the way from Chinese to French - and from fast food to haute cuisine. In all, the city is home to more than 12,000 restaurants serving 62 different types of cuisine.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Vancouver.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6046261" lat="41.383625" long="2.174550">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Barcelona</location>
            <state>Spain</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Architecture of Antonio Gaudi]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Barcelona's undisputed claims to fame are the fantastical buildings of Antonio Gaudi, the renowned Spanish architect who designed a series of neo-gothic structures near the city center. Stroll the Passieg de Gracia, where La Pedrera and Casa Batlio, two of Gaudi's most famous works, await. Or simply jump into Barcelona's thriving cafe and bar culture - sip a beer at a sidewalk table in the Gracia district and watch the world go by.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Toronto.png]]></image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="cities" reg="US">
    <row locid="10322" lat="34.043397" long="-118.445854">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>New York City</location>
        <state>New York</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Rodeo Drive]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Hit New York City for the definitive urban adventure, whether that means catching Broadway musicals or experimental plays, shopping at the world's highest of high end stores, or just marveling at the lights in Times Square. Bargains on museums, galleries, concerts, and sporting events can be found any day of the week. And be sure to bring your appetite - the world's greatest chefs and the perfect hot dog alike can be found in the Big Apple.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_losangeles.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="10322" lat="34.043397" long="-118.445854">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Los Angeles</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Rodeo Drive]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[With streets lined with palms, Los Angeles is an ultra-happening haven to stars and those who seek them. But it's also a world-class cultural capital, where you can spend the day absorbed in art at the J. Paul Getty Center or absorb the rays in bohemian Venice Beach. Nibble cuisine at one of countless celebrity-haunted eateries around town, or hit shops on Rodeo Drive or in funky Melrose. This home to Hollywood is the place to see and be seen.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_losangeles.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6003647" lat="41.851496" long="-87.628071">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Chicago</location>
        <state>Illinois</state>
        <site><![CDATA[America's Second City]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[From the top of Sears Tower to the shores of Lake Michigan, Chicago is a city made for urban adventurers. Explore the city from the El, and don't miss Wrigley Field and the Art Institute. Stroll the Magnificent Mile for fine dining among historical landmarks, or venture to Millennium Park, where celebrity architects have created an inspiring urban playground. Looking for nightlife? You'll dig the Second City's hot blues clubs.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Chicago.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6004910" lat="37.798430" long="-122.407489">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Francisco</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Chinatown]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Those on a quest for the ultra hip need look no further than San Francisco. From the Beat Generation haunts of North Beach to the trendy Union Square core, you'll discover colorful characters, adventurous cuisine, and architectural wonders around every picturesque corner. Visitors of all persuasions enjoy strolling out-and-proud Castro Street, and no trip would be complete without taking in the majestic Golden Gate Bridge from the park.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_SanFrancisco.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3121" lat="47.621862" long="-122.309731">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Seattle</location>
        <state>Washington</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Space Needle]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[If you know Seattle only for its coffee and software, you've just started to experience the energy and originality this urban hot spot has to offer. Start among the produce stalls and buskers at Pike Place Market, or rock out at the Experience Music Project. Spend the day in a kayak on Lake Union or take in the skyline and mountains from the Space Needle, then head downtown for superb shopping and the region's coolest indie music scene.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Seattle.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="99046" lat="33.742267" long="-84.340117">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Atlanta</location>
        <state>Georgia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[World of Coca-Cola]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Southern hospitality meets global sophistication in Atlanta, Georgia. Start your visit downtown, where news junkies can make a pilgrimage to CNN Center and the whole family will enjoy the marvels at World of Coca-Cola&reg;. Ready to shop? Venture to the high-end Buckhead district for classy boutiques amid gorgeous southern mansions. Be sure to hit the High Art Museum, too. It's just one of many examples of the city's passion for the arts.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Atlanta.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="9173" lat="25.914030" long="-80.198641">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Miami</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Famous nightlife]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Salsa dancing, art deco architecture, and wide stretches of sand - where else can you be but Miami? The city's nightlife is glorious and notorious, drawing spirited pleasure seekers from around the world. Linger over dinner at any number of fine dining destinations, and discover the newest trends in this fashion epicenter. Whether you're looking for a shopping adventure or are on a quest for the best Cuban music, Miami's big-city beat is calling.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Miami.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Boston</location>
        <state>Massachusetts</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Faneuil Hall is a collection of boutiques.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Urban sophisticates and sophisticated sports fans consider Boston a must-see destination. It's not hard to see why. The Boston Pops is one of the world's most renowned orchestras, and Red Sox Nation has been unrelenting since their curse-breaking 2004 World Series victory. You won't want to miss Fanueuil Hall to shop its boutiques and pushcart vendors, and a visit to Harvard Yard's overstuffed bookstores is a must for serious readers.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_Boston.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2434" lat="29.970688" long="-90.052760">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>New Orleans</location>
        <state>Louisiana</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Architecture in French Quarter]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Resilient and brilliant, New Orleans lets nothing stop its vibrant nightlife. It all starts with America's most creative music and food. Catch a stellar jam session at Preservation Hall, then savor shrimp etouffee in one of the French Quarter's Creole eateries. Explore the stately architecture of the Garden District or tour an old plantation on the outskirts of town. Locals call it "Nawlins." You'll call it the most fun you've had in ages.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_NewOrleans.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3763" lat="38.899239" long="-77.041615">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Washington</location>
        <state>District of Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Nightlife of Georgetown.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Whether you're liberal or conservative, there's one thing you'll find agreement about - Washington, D.C. means business when it comes to urban fun. When you've had your fill of monuments and museums, enjoy waterfront shopping and nightlife in Georgetown. Experience a show in the grandeur of the Kennedy Center. Hungry? Catch a glimpse at who's dining at the next table in top-rated steak houses where Capitol Hill's power brokers gather.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/bright%20lights/brightlights_WashingtonDC.png]]></image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="dining" reg="intl">
      <row locid="178671" lat="48.855250" long="2.345432">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Paris</location>
        <state>France</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Food in Paris isn't restricted to French food.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Paris's culinary delights are legendary. The city is home to Le Cordon Bleu, a renowned cooking academy, and it's where Julia Child first rose to stardom. Browse the city's lively markets and discover bakeries, cheese shops, and wine bars. When the dinner bell tolls, choose from countless bistros, haute cuisine hotspots, and neighborhood cafes. Prepare for variety, too - Parisian restaurants serve cuisines from across the globe.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="179096" lat="41.901961" long="12.388971">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Rome</location>
        <state>Italy</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Campo de' Fiori]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Rome's delightful cuisine is reflective of Italy's varied culture. Begin your gourmet experience in Rome with a trip to the Campo de' Fiori, a picturesque outdoor market where stalls overflow with fruits, vegetables, meats, cheeses, and breads. Head to a sidewalk cafe for a wood-fired Neapolitan pizza and a glass of Prosecco. And finish your day with a dish of spaghetti carbonara and a bottle of Barolo, one of the country's signature red wines.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6004910" lat="37.75773" long="-122.446093">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Barcelona</location>
        <state>Spain</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Catalonia's diverse cuisine.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Located on the shores of the Mediterranean - and in the heart of Spain's vibrant Catalonia region - Barcelona is a city obsessed with food. Walk into any one of the city's casual tapas bars, where small plates of local delicacies are served in warm, inviting atmospheres. Or score a seat at an exotic bistro - the city is loaded with cutting-edge cuisine. However you define gourmet, Barcelona has a table for you.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2998" lat="-22.905119" long="-43.254064">
        <region>South America</region>
        <location>Rio de Janeiro</location>
        <state>Brazil</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Churrasco (Brazilian Steak Houses)]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Rio's beaches and nightlife are justly celebrated, but the city's cuisine alone is worth the trip. You'll find loads of international flavors here, but Brazilian cooking takes center stage. Sample the Feijoada, a beef, pork, and bean stew served with rice and kale. Don't miss the rollicking churrascarias, which serve grilled meats and vegetables. Finally, walk the length of Ipanema beach, where waterfront eateries serve superb grilled seafood.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="55419" lat="-37.829316" long="144.957043">
        <region>Asia</region>
        <location>Melbourne</location>
        <state>Australia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Yarra Valley, renouned wine region in Southern Australia.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Bring your appetite for culinary adventure to Melbourne's Chinatown, located in the city center, which is loaded with top-flight Chinese, Malaysian, Thai, Vietnamese, Indonesian, and Japanese restaurants. Embark on a day of wine tasting in the Yarra Valley, 30 minutes east of the city, where you'll discover excellent chardonnay and pinot noir. Finally, head to St. Kilda, a seaside neighborhood dotted with cozy pubs and seafood houses.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="57382" lat="49.341952" long="-123.203481">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Vancouver</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Davie Street]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Vancouver is one of Canada's most diverse cities - over half of its residents speak a first language other than English. So it only makes sense that the city's cuisine would be as multicultural as its population. Sample the city's fresh seafood, sushi, and Indian cuisine or explore bistro-laden Davie Street in the bustling West End district. Still hungry? Hit Robson Street to enjoy sweet or savory cr&ecirc;pes, perfect any time of day.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4135" lat="49.478088" long="-119.600704">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Okanagan Valley</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[There are 74 wineries.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[British Columbia's Okanagan Valley is beginning to turn wine lovers' heads. Explore the world's northernmost winemaking region, home to 74 wineries. Winemakers here craft vintages that are reminiscent of those found in Germany, Austria, France, and Italy, guaranteeing you'll have a delightfully worldly tasting experience. And you can't go wrong when you dine in charming eateries specializing in the perfect fare to complement your glass of vino.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4135" lat="49.478088" long="-119.600704">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Okanagan Valley</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[There are 74 wineries.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[British Columbia's Okanagan Valley is beginning to turn wine lovers' heads. Explore the world's northernmost winemaking region, home to 74 wineries. Winemakers here craft vintages that are reminiscent of those found in Germany, Austria, France, and Italy, guaranteeing you'll have a delightfully worldly tasting experience. And you can't go wrong when you dine in charming eateries specializing in the perfect fare to complement your glass of vino.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="11617" lat="18.232843" long="-63.050104">
        <region>St. Martin/St. Maarten</region>
        <location>St. Martin/St. Maarten</location>
        <state>Anguilla</state>
        <site><![CDATA[CuisinArt culinary institute.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Famous for its French cuisine, St. Martin is widely recognized as the culinary capital of the Caribbean. Feast on a menu that is as widely varied as the island's colorful history, with Creole, Dutch, English, and farther-flung influences. After dinner, belly up to a beachfront bar and order a glass of the legendary Guavaberry liqueur, a folk beverage made from local berries and rum. Yum!]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="181111" lat="26.777547" long="-77.329665">
        <region>Caribbean</region>
        <location>Green Turtle Cay</location>
        <state>Bahamas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Historic Graycliff]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Bahamas offer a wealth of superb restaurants. Experience the Caribbean's only five-star restaurant: Graycliff, a mansion built in 1742 that features a 250,000-bottle wine cellar and award-winning cigar factory. For a more affordable night out, sample some of the local seafood, including conch, a tasty white meat from a large ocean mollusk that's often served in salads, chowders, gumbos, or burgers.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="182123" lat="22.259665" long="114.002680">
        <region>Asia</region>
        <location>Hong Kong</location>
        <state>China</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Hong Kong has a reputation of Gourmet Paradise]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Hong Kong's cuisine is an incredible melange of cultures, ideas, and ingredients. Experience Dim Sum, an Asian tradition of steamed meats, seafood, and vegetables served by a rotating cast of waiters. Dine at a famed haute cuisine establishment helmed by a world-famous chef for a meal that you will never forget. Or simply partake of the daily Yum Cha ("drinking tea") that is an integral part of Hong Kong life.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="dining" reg="US">
      <row locid="9173" lat="25.914030" long="-80.198641">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Miami</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Wide range of dining options]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Miami is where the flavors of the Caribbean and Latin America come to dance. Dine on fish caught just that morning off the coast, prepared by a master chef. Experience every meaning of the word "salsa" in epicurean hangouts where the food - and music - are hot. But it's not all delectable Cuban cuisine in this worldly way station for hungry travelers. You'll discover some of the most delicious Italian, Thai, and Mediterranean dishes here as well.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_Miami.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6004910" lat="40.668622" long="-73.976652">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>New York</location>
        <state>New York</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Chocolate is New York City's leading specialty-food export.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[New York City is <em>the</em> city for serious foodies. Grab breakfast on your way to the subway in any of the city's eateries specializing in comfort food. For hot corned beef on rye or the bagel by which all other bagels are measured, you can't go wrong at any of the city's famous kosher delis. Dinner time? Hit top-rated steak houses and order yours medium rare. Then, for dessert, taste heaven one sample at time at Manhattan's legendary chocolatiers.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_NewYork.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3132" lat="37.75773" long="-122.446093">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Francisco</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Cliff House]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[San Francisco welcomes adventurous palates. Explore the Noe Valley neighborhood, where world-renowned chefs turn farm-fresh ingredients into masterpieces. If you're in the mood for sweet and sour, head to Chinatown, the dim sum mecca. Fall for the Mission District's famously filling (and affordable) burritos, or the hottest of California Street's haute cuisine. This is the city where bold international flavors dare to be original.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_SanFrancisco.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1503" lat="29.790767" long="-95.371374">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Houston</location>
        <state>Texas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[There are more than 5,000 restaurants]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Houston, we've got an appetite. Recently rated by ForbesTraveler.com as one of the best restaurant cities in America, this gourmand's getaway offers more than 5,000 eateries representing more than 35 countries and American regions. Start with a Texas-sized steak at one of the city's legendary steakhouses or try some world-class sushi. And it may be stating the obvious, but this is the city to satisfy your craving for Tex-Mex.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_Houston.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6895" lat="41.880606" long="-88.203261">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Chicago</location>
        <state>Illinois</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Chicago deep dish pizza]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Infused with flavors from Italy, Eastern Europe, and the American heartland, Chicago lures epicureans looking for memorable meals. Grab a Polish sausage at Wrigley Field, or sample the international fare downtown. Sink your teeth into some thick-crusted Chicago-style pizza or slice into sirloin at one of the city's legendary steakhouses. Interested in dessert? There's nothing more delicious than a slice of Windy City cheesecake.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_Chicago.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2434" lat="29.970688" long="-90.052760">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>New Orleans</location>
        <state>Louisiana</state>
        <site><![CDATA[More restaurants are open in New Orleans than ever before]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[New Orleans, where Cajun and Creole cuisine were born, is where epicureans come to dine. Seek out the joints where celebrity chefs like Emeril Lagasse, Paul Prudhome, and John Besh deliver once-in-a-lifetime culinary experiences. Even off-the-beaten path restaurants serve up mouth-watering jambalayas, etouffes, and the tastiest cornbread on the Mississippi. One tip - seek out the bananas foster. It's on fire. Literally!]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_NewOrleans.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="10322" lat="34.043397" long="-118.445854">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Los Angeles</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Star watch at famous restaurants like the Ivy.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Los Angeles feeds famous appetites, and is famous for its fresh and healthy food. Here the best dishes of Mexico and Asia come to party. Journey to Olvera street for crunchy taquitos or sip sake at any number of the city's refined sushi bars. The City of Angels offers both grab-and-go burgers way tastier than they have to be and spa cuisine at high-end eateries where stars strike deals. Discover for yourself why foodies live and dine in LA.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_LosAngeles.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="9169" lat="36.228422" long="-115.118527">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Las Vegas</location>
        <state>Nevada</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Celebrity and world famous chefs]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Dining has been redefined in Las Vegas. Sure, you can still grab affordable (and incredibly tasty) buffet fare, but the past decade has seen a migration of the world's greatest chefs to the Strip. Let master sommeliers guide your wine experience in restaurants so beautifully designed you'll forget you're in a casino. Let others hit the jackpot at the blackjack table. The true treasure here is the worldly cuisine.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_LasVegas.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6141" lat="38.299299" long="-122.300639">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Napa</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[French Laundry]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The rolling fields of Napa Valley beckon many a wine-lover, with hundreds of wineries to choose from. But something has to go with the wine, right? Start with five-star The French Laundry, where fresh, meticulously-selected local ingredients are transformed into gustatory wonders. Drop in on countless chic bistros and order what's in season. You'll always find the perfect complement to whatever you're drinking.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_Napa.png</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2759" lat="45.523501" long="-122.617284">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Portland</location>
        <state>Oregon</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Oregons wine country]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[A food revolution is underway in Portland, Oregon. Locally-grown, organic ingredients are on the menu everywhere - even the burger joints make their fries with spuds grown in the Willamette Valley. Sip the products of Oregon's wine country in hip, downtown wine bars. Explore Asian, Mediterranean, and vegan flavors at one of the city's food festivals or farmers' markets. And beer lovers take note - Portland's microbreweries rule.]]></description>
        <image>/daily/testarea/slee/tripfinder/tfimages/Dining\Dining_Portland.png</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="escapes" reg="intl">
        <row locid="2855" lat="18.159629" long="-76.387238">
            <region>Caribbean</region>
            <location>Port Antonio</location>
            <state>Jamaica</state>
            <site><![CDATA[James Bond Beach]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Jamaica's beaches are the stuff of legend. Where else can you lounge in the sand on James Bond Beach before retiring to the bar at the Goldeneye Hotel, where Bond writer Ian Fleming once lived? After indulging your inner 007, visit Blue Lagoon Beach, which hosted Brooke Shields during the filming of <em>Blue Lagoon</em>. Or take a dip at Seven Mile Beach, a '60s hotspot that still sports a carefree vibe - and the occasional nude sunbather.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Jamaica.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="935" lat="21.095766" long="-86.818376">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Cancun</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Quintana Roo]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Retreat to Canc&uacute;n's famed white sand beaches, which are now more spacious than ever. (Local tourism officials doubled the width of the area's beaches in 2005.) Bask in the region's perfect temperatures - which average 78 degrees year-round - and snorkel, swim, and dive in Canc&uacute;n's crystal-clear Caribbean waters. Whether you dig beaches, islands, water, sun, or all of the above, Canc&uacute;n has it all.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Cancun.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2519" lat="25.079786" long="-77.341063">
            <region>Caribbean</region>
            <location>Nassau</location>
            <state>Bahamas</state>
            <site><![CDATA[New Providence]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[The beaches of the Bahamas are famous for their sugar-white sand, sparkling waters, and jet set sunbathers. (An exception to the white-sand beaches: gorgeous Pink Sands Beach, on Grand Bahamas Island.) Fly by seaplane to the Out Islands, where you can angle for bonefish on tropical sands so secluded you may not see another person. Or visit a protected beach and learn about the efforts to conserve the islands' beautiful coral reefs.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Bahamas.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6051765" lat="36.382744" long="25.445944">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Santorini</location>
            <state>Greece</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Pyrgos]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Set sail for the Greek Islands, the mythical home of the goddess Hera - on the island of Samos, you can explore the ruins of the Heraion, a temple dedicated to the goddess. But don't spend too long on Samos; Greece has more than 1,400 other islands, with countless miles of unspoiled shoreline. Be sure to revel in the quiet coves, pulsating clubs, and romantic bistros of Santorini and Mykonos, the country's two most popular isles.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[<http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6058399" lat="48.458787" long="-123.413291">
            <region>North America</region>
            <location>Victoria</location>
            <state>British Columbia</state>
            <site><![CDATA[The Butchart Gardens]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Experience Canadian coastal living at its best in Victoria, a seaside city that offers myriad opportunities for sailing, fishing, kayaking, and whale-watching. Amble through the immaculate grounds of the Butchart Gardens, a 55-acre garden that's home to blooming flora year-round. Stroll Victoria's historical harbor and explore its vibrant downtown. However you choose to relax, you'll do it in comfort: Victoria has the mildest climate in Canada.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Victoria.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2998" lat="-22.905119" long="-43.254064">
            <region>South America</region>
            <location>Rio de Janeiro</location>
            <state>Brazil</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Ipanema Beach]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Escape to the famous sands of Rio de Janiero, one of the world's most iconic beachfront destinations. Catch some rays on Ipanema Beach, which gave its name to the bossa nova classic "The Girl from Ipanema." Walk the white sands of Copacabana Beach, ranked as one of the world's top ten. In February, the famous Carnival fills the streets with parades and all-night parties, but Rio's carefree, high-spirited atmosphere persists throughout the year.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_RiodeJaniero.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="500187" lat="10.292911" long="-85.849339">
            <region>South America</region>
            <location>Tamarindo</location>
            <state>Costa Rica</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Jaco Beach, a surfer's mecca]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Costa Rica is home to many different sands - here you'll find white, gray, beige, brown, and even black sand. Tickle your toes in the sugary stuff on the country's Caribbean side, or explore tide pools on the rocky stretches of the Pacific coast. Discover beachfront luxury at Tamarindo, where you can view sea turtles, catch waves, and delight in tropical mango scrubs. And don't miss Jaco Beach, replete with waves, nightclubs, and top-flight dining.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_CostaRica.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="500187" lat="10.292911" long="-85.849339">
            <region>Riviera Maya</region>
            <location>Riviera Maya</location>
            <state>Riviera Maya</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Jaco Beach, a surfer's mecca]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mexican sun seems to shine brighter on the Riviera Maya. Relax on Tulum's lengthy beaches, which are free of crashing surf and lie within minutes of the area's Mayan ruins. Stay in a beachside cabana at the budget-friendly Xpu-Ha Beach area, a rustic community that caters to backpackers and adventurers. Or simply grab a margarita and kick back beneath a beach umbrella at Playa del Carmen, a quaint seaside village.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_CostaRica.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="9306" lat="12.595156" long="-70.051478">
            <region>Caribbean</region>
            <location>Palm Beach</location>
            <state>Aruba</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Manchebo Beach]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[It's hard to argue against a place that gets over 300 days of sun every year, has spacious white-sand beaches and a vibrant culture blending Spanish, Dutch, and Indian influences. Restore your peace of mind at Baby Beach, which sits on a shallow, clear lagoon where you can snorkel amongst parrot fish, angel fish, and assorted tropical species. Or head to Manchebo Beach, a wide, sandy oasis that's Aruba's only topless sunning spot.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Aruba.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="9306" lat="12.595156" long="-70.051478">
            <region>Phuket</region>
            <location>Phuket</location>
            <state>Phuket</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Manchebo Beach]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Phuket, an island province located in Southern Thailand, offers miles of pristine tropical shores and affordable lodgings. Snorkel, scuba, and swim the days away on palm-lined beaches, renowned for their clear waters and sparkling sands. Pamper yourself with beachfront massages and spa treatments at one of the area's superb luxury resorts, or indulge your passion for shopping at the Jungycelon Shopping Mall, home to over 200 name-brand stores.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Aruba.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="9306" lat="12.595156" long="-70.051478">
            <region>Los Cabos</region>
            <location>Los Cabos</location>
            <state>Los Cabos</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Manchebo Beach]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Located on the Southern tip of Mexico's Baja California, Los Cabos offers some of the Pacific coast's most picturesque beaches. Pack a picnic and a bottle of wine before taking a boat to the secluded Lover's Beach, which offers incredible views of nearby natural rock arches. Or share the sunshine with the family at Playa el Medano, a calm and popular swimming spot. But if hanging ten is your M.O., then don't miss Los Cerritos, a premier surfing beach.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Aruba.png]]></image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="escapes" reg="US">
      <row locid="2491" lat="33.737337" long="-78.895569">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Myrtle Beach</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Beach activities]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach boasts 60 - count 'em, 60 - miles of white sandy beaches. As if that wasn't enough, this perennial vacation paradise lures visitors with more than 100  courses worthy of the pros. Traveling with kids? Put the putter in their hands at any of the 46 fun-themed courses. Whether you'd like to get out of a sand trap or let the little ones bury you in sand, this Atlantic coast getaway is serious fun.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Myrtle.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6033" lat="27.916665" long="-82.736915">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Clearwater - St Petersburg</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Family friendly beaches]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[St. Petersburg, Florida has a reputation as a spring break mecca, luring visitors with its powdery sands. But it's also an oasis of calm, a warm-weather destination of lush gardens and farmers' markets. For an even more low-key getaway, head to nearby Clearwater, a romantic seaside village ideal for taking in the sunset. With an abundance of shopping, golf, and family entertainment, these Gulf Coast beach retreats promise a relaxing escape.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_clearwater.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1219" lat="41.425297" long="-82.695621">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Fort Lauderdale</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[23 miles of 'sun kissed beaches']]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Instead of a welcome mat, Fort Lauderdale spreads out 23 miles of sun-kissed beaches. Start the day with some snorkeling and discover the sea life teeming just below the surface. Stroll the sands at dusk, then head to the Riverwalk Arts and Entertainment district, where you can shop at luxury boutiques and dine in top-notch eateries. It's easy to get around in this canal-laced city - just grab a water taxi and set your course for adventure.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_FtLauderdale.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1219" lat="41.425297" long="-82.695621">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Cape Cod</location>
        <state>Massachusetts</state>
        <site><![CDATA[23 miles of 'sun kissed beaches']]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[When you first set foot in Cape Cod, you'll find a string of villages full of weathered shingles, whaling captains' mansions, lobster shacks, and upscale dining discoveries. Go on a quest to find the most picturesque lighthouse amid the wind-swept dunes. Find out for yourself what makes Martha's Vineyard the preferred weekend escape for the well-connected. And don't miss the famously charming village of Nantucket.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_FtLauderdale.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3179" lat="18.438016" long="-66.054216">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Juan</location>
        <state>Puerto Rico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[A quick flight from the US mainland]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[You can drive around the coast of Puerto Rico in a day, but why hurry through one of the world's greatest adventure escapes? Hit Ca&ntilde;a Gorda beach for scuba diving and other family-oriented water sport activities. Hike into lush Guanica Forest Reserve and swim through the bioluminescent lagoon at Vieques. Or head inland to sip the offerings at coffee plantations or the harder stuff at any number of friendly bars and restaurants.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_PuertoRico.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3073" lat="32.786977" long="-117.157818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Diego</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[70 miles of beautiful beaches]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Surfers trek to San Diego's 70 miles of beaches to catch the perfect wave, but there's more to the city than hanging ten. Head over to the Children's Pool to watch seals and sea lions sunning themselves, or stroll the boardwalk at Mission Beach. Take an introductory scuba course at the gentle La Jolla shores, home to an ecological preserve. When you've had your fill of surf, San Diego beckons with ample food, shopping, and entertainment.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_SanDiego.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2297" lat="25.760422" long="-80.339081">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Miami</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[World famous South Beach]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Sunshine, sand, and salsa make Miami a beach lover's paradise. Start at South Beach, the world famous recreation capital. Take a dip in the warm ocean waves, then immerse yourself in the music of Little Havana or sample delectable modern cuisine in the Art Deco District. Kids will love a trip to the zoo, while adults will enjoy a zoo of another sort - Miami's exuberant nightlife, spilling from numerous bars and nightclubs.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_Maimi.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="5922" lat="26.114804" long="-97.166396">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>South Padre Island</location>
        <state>Texas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[34 miles of beautiful beaches]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Visitors yearning for relaxation - and more than 300 species of birds - flock to South Padre Island, off the southern tip of Texas. Don't forget your bird guide and binoculars! In this ecologically rich getaway you can go horseback riding on the beach, hike, parasail, scuba dive, golf, or try your hand at deep sea fishing. After a day lazing along the 34 miles of beach, sample the fresh seafood at any number of excellent restaurants with outdoor seating.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_clearwater.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="5922" lat="26.114804" long="-97.166396">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Oahu</location>
        <state>Hawaii</state>
        <site><![CDATA[34 miles of beautiful beaches]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[You're going to wish that "aloha" didn't also mean "goodbye" when you venture to Oahu. Start by bathing in sunshine on world famous Waikiki Beach. Name the water activity and you'll find it on Hawaii's most populous island, from snorkeling to parasailing, surfing to sunset cruises. Get off the well-worn path with a hike to Makapuu Lighthouse on the South Shore or take hula lessons on the beach. You'll come to believe that Oahu means paradise.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_clearwater.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="55032" lat="13.154165" long="-59.579846">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>St. Thomas</location>
        <state>US Virgin Islands</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Known as 'America's Paradise']]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Dip your toes in the sapphire shallows off Magens Bay Beach. Watch the palms sway while sipping a banana daiquiri prepared with Cruzan rum. Are you in paradise? Close. When your journey takes you to St. Thomas, U.S. Virgin Islands, you'll pinch yourself to make sure you're not dreaming. Don't miss Drake's Seat, the vantage point where Sir Francis Drake watched his fleet. You, on the other hand, will be watching a breathtaking sunset.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/beach/beach_StThomas.png]]></image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="experiences" reg="indy">
      <row locid="3687" lat="45.401659" long="12.350157">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Venice</location>
        <state>Italy</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Mysterious Venice</site>
        <description><![CDATA[You've never seen Venice like this. Roam the city that the European Renaissance revealed as a hotbed of intrigue, mystery, and sweepingly romantic vistas. Experience gorgeous architectural and historical structures by day while getting a glimpse of the city's secret history by night. From Gondola tours in shimmering canals to molten stoves in glassblowing studios, the glorious history of Venice will come alive for you.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/Italy_mysterious_venice.jpg]]></image>
        <sticker><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/sticker_italy.png]]></sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="6048918" lat="40.070500" long="116.579500">
        <region>Asia</region>
        <location>Beijing</location>
        <state>China</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Dragons and Ancient Warriors</site>
        <description><![CDATA[Pack your bags for a journey like no other as you discover the history, beauty, and intrigue of China. Gaze upon imperial treasures, travel by rickshaw, and dine on traditional cuisine. Discover all Beijing has to offer, including the Temple of Heaven, legendary Tiananmen Square, and the Forbidden City. From the frenetic energy of Shanghai to the magnificent Great Wall of China, your adventures in this enchanting country await.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/China_dragons_ancient_warriors.jpg]]></image>
        <sticker><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/sticker_china.png]]></sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="767" lat="30.032250" long="31.322154">
        <region>Middle East</region>
        <location>Cairo</location>
        <state>Egypt</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Quest of the Ancient Kings</site>
        <description><![CDATA[Explore Egypt's ancient civilization and the world's most iconic monuments. Visit awe-inspiring World Heritage sites and marvel at the country's rugged grandeur. Immerse yourself in the local culture by wandering Cairo's bazaars, or visit one of the ancient wonders of the world&#8212;the magnificent pyramids. From a Nile cruise to urban excursions, the cultural treasures and stunning landscapes of Egypt are waiting to be discovered.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/Egypt_questofancientkings.jpg]]></image>
        <sticker><![CDATA[tfimages/indy/sticker_egypt.png]]></sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="177865" lat="28.549000" long="77.203500">
        <region>Asia</region>
        <location>New Delhi</location>
        <state>India</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Palaces, Temples and Wildlife</site>
        <description><![CDATA[With a rich mix of culture, natural beauty, and archaeological wonder, India is a world-class destination drawing visitors from around the globe. Embark on an adventure to one of the world's last remaining tiger habitats, or visit the humbling ghats of Varnasi. Escape to the World Heritage sites of Fatehpur Sikri and the magnificent Taj Majal. From rugged hillsides to man-made structures that will leave you in awe, your adventures in India await.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/India_palaces_temples_wildlife.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_india.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="375" lat="31.967833" long="35.907008">
        <region>Middle East</region>
        <location>Amman</location>
        <state>Jordan</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Ruins and Desert</site>
        <description><![CDATA[From sweeping desert vistas to ancient artifacts, Jordan is a country filled with new discoveries. Embark on a fascinating day trip from Amman to the ancient city of Jerash&#8212;only an hour away, but a trip 2000 years back in time. Walk the grounds believed to be the sites of five ancient biblical cities&#8212;Sodom, Gomorrah, Admah, Zebouin, and Zoar. Explore Jordan's treasures and meet its people on a wonder-filled trip of a lifetime.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/Jordan_ruins_desert.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_jordan.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="935" lat="21.095766" long="-86.818376">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Cancun</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Myans, Jungles, and Beach</site>
        <description><![CDATA[Explore the undiscovered side of Mexico. Walk amongst the ruins of the ancient cities of Chichen Itza, Uxmal, and Coba. Take a side trip to explore the Cenote Dzitnup, a subterranean cavern filled with crystal blue water. Then experience the pristine beaches of Cancun or the sub-tropical rainforests found just outside the cities and towns. From ancient temples to ecological wonders, Mexico is an oasis just waiting for you to explore.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/Mexico_mayans_jungles_beach.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_mexico.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="1938" lat="27.712234" long="85.318107">
        <region>Asia</region>
        <location>Kathmandu</location>
        <state>Nepal</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Kingdoms, Mountains - Jungle</site>
        <description><![CDATA[A land of breathtaking landscapes, engaging culture, and rich history, Nepal is yours to experience. Through guided tours and self exploration, you'll traverse forests, discover isolated hamlets, and visit World Heritage sites. Embark on a jungle safari adventure, or just unwind with a leisurely rafting trip down the Trisuli River. Wonders never cease in the awe-inspiring land of Nepal.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/nepal_kingdoms_mountains.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_nepal.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="2077" lat="-12.075524" long="-77.084545">
        <region>South America</region>
        <location>Lima</location>
        <state>Peru</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Jungle, Ruins and Beyond</site>
        <description><![CDATA[From the imposing peaks of the Andes to the beauty of the Nazca desert, Peru is a country where you'll find an enthralling blend of cultures amid spectacular natural beauty. Start by exploring the Incan cities of Caral and Nazca and conclude with a memorable visit to the "Lost City of the Incas," Machu Picchu. In this, one of the world's newest Seven Wonders, you'll discover marvelous Incan ruins and scenery that will take your breath away.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/Peru_worldofincas.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_peru_incas.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="178042" lat="-13.171469" long="-72.549163">
        <region>South America</region>
        <location>Machu Picchu</location>
        <state>Peru</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Forgotton World of the Incas</site>
        <description><![CDATA[By foot, plane, canoe, and train, explore the wondrous country of Peru. Embark on a spectacular trip that covers the mysterious Amazon Jungle, as well as the ancient Incan capital and World Heritage site of Cuzco. Trek to an eco-friendly jungle lodge where you'll learn from multilingual nature guides about the area's rich flora and fauna. Conclude your adventure with a memorable visit to the "Lost City of the Incas," Machu Picchu.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/Peru_jungle_ruins.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_peru_ruins.png</sticker>
      </row>
      <row locid="160167" lat="41.177634" long="-111.943944">
        <region>USA</region>
        <location>Zion National Park</location>
        <state>Utah</state>
        <site><![CDATA[]]>Trail of the Navajo Indians</site>
        <description><![CDATA[From awe-inspiring landscapes to heart-pounding experiences, your adventure in the American desert awaits. Hike or travel by horseback against a backdrop of spectacular scenery. Walk the paths of the Navajo Indians as you venture into the wonderland of Zion National Park and the breathtaking Bryce Canyon. Peer over the edge of the vast Grand Canyon, or try your luck in glitzy Las Vegas. Memories of a lifetime are yours for the making in the USA.]]></description>
        <image>tfimages/indy/US_trailofnavajo.jpg</image>
        <sticker>tfimages/indy/sticker_usa.png</sticker>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="outdoors" reg="intl">
      <row locid="4115" lat="50.117215" long="-122.969467">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Whistler</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Aerial sightseeing to Ziptrekking]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[It's a fact: There's endless activity in Whistler when the snow melts. From aerial sightseeing to Ziptrekking, summertime in Whistler means nonstop outdoor recreation. Take the kids to the Adventure Zone, a mecca of fun that offers horseback rides, mini-golf, and trampolines, or head for the Westcoaster Luge, a summer sled course with banked turns and screaming straightaways. However you get your kicks, Whistler has an activity for you.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="10550" lat="51.184235" long="-115.564903">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Banff-Jasper</location>
        <state>Alberta</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Hiking mountain trails]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[With its towering peaks, cascading waterfalls, and numerous hot springs, Banff National Park is one of Canada's most popular tourist attractions. Hike the area's many miles of trails, winding your way through old growth forests, sub-alpine valleys, or high mountain ridges. Kayak or canoe on the azure waters of Lake Louise and view the area's abundant wildlife, including elk, grizzly and black bears, moose, mountain goats, and bighorn sheep.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4005" lat="45.518587" long="-73.650968">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Mont Tremblant</location>
        <state>Quebec</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Four Seasons Resort in Canada]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Mont Tremblant, located only 90 minutes from downtown Montreal, is one of the most lively and active year-round resorts in Canada - this quaint resort town is known for its many parades, concerts, and festivals. Ride the gondola to the summit of the highest peak in the Laurentians, where spectacular views await. Or simply revel in the area's many summertime activities, including mountain biking, hiking, golfing, canoeing, and swimming.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="181783" lat="50.458084" long="-116.230201">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Panorama</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Whitewater rafting]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Journey to the heart of the Kootenay Rockies, where Panorama resort offers a full slate of activities. Treat the family to an unforgettable whitewater rafting trip on Toby Creek. Hike along mountain trails, fish in glacial lakes, and explore the mountainside on horseback. Cap it off with a mountain bike adventure in the Kona Bike Park, where a high-speed chairlift provides riders with access to 20 awesome trails.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="181791" lat="50.883738" long="-119.888939">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Sun Peaks</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[2,000 hours of sunshine a year!]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Sun Peaks Resort in the heart of mountainous southern British Columbia boasts a staggering array of summertime activities; trail rides, canoe tours, and ATV adventures are just the beginning. Sign up for a bike clinic and gain valuable new skills in the Bike Park at Sun Peaks, or embark on a guided fly-fishing tour. And with 16 hiking trails and a children's sport camp, Sun Peaks delivers fun for the whole family.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6050949" lat="45.943334" long="6.889314">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>French Alps</location>
        <state>France</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Chamonix, Megeve and Val d'Isere]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Sculpted by glaciers and wind, the French Alps are one of nature's most stunning creations. The Alps are dotted with over 200 resorts - including Megeve and Val d'Isere - and summertime means pleasant weather, green valleys, and fields of wildflowers. Ride the world's highest cable car at Chamonix, hike through the region's three national parks, stroll through the lantern-lit lanes of Annency, or even learn to paraglide at Le Grand Bornand.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3286" lat="59.330616" long="18.010339">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Stockholm</location>
        <state>Sweden</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Scandinavian Mountain Range]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[In the northern regions of Sweden, the Scandinavian Mountains bathe in the long light of the arctic summer. Tour the area's picturesque national parks, including Sarek, Stora Sjöfallet ("Big Falls"), and Muddus. Canoe, kayak, and fish on the many lakes and rivers of this striking northland. And witness the nomadic lifestlye of the Sami, a native people who have herded reindeer here for over 12,000 years. Sweden beckons with natural beauty.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3209" lat="14.051005" long="-60.973384">
        <region>Caribbean</region>
        <location>Castries</location>
        <state>St. Lucia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Rain forests]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Caribbean isn't commonly associated with mountain terrain, but the island of St. Lucia is home to a pair of striking peaks: the 2,400-foot-plus Pitons. (Climbing here is for experts only; the best views are from neighboring Mt. Gimie.) Hike through 19,000 acres of lush rainforest - prime territory for bird watchers and nature lovers. Or witness geological history at Sulphur Springs, a dormant volcano that you can actually drive a car into.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2077" lat="-12.075524" long="-77.084545">
        <region>South America</region>
        <location>Lima</location>
        <state>Peru</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Peruvvian Amazonia and Macchu Picchu]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Lima is the ideal starting point for once-in-a-lifetime adventures to the legendary ruins at Macchu Picchu and the lush, Peruvian Amazon. Explore the lost city of the Incas, a UNESCO World Heritage Site recently named one of the New Seven Wonders of the World. Hike or mountain bike amid the misty peaks of the Andes, recharging your batteries at Cusco before embarking on the rest of your unforgettable journey.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Swiss Alps</location>
        <state>Switzerland</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Laden with glaciers, towering peaks, and flower-covered alpine valleys, the Swiss Alps are one of Europe's most scenic regions. Hike or bike the trails at Verbier, a legendary resort. Savor the alpine dusk at a summer street party in Zermatt, a mountain retreat that sits at the northern base of the Matterhorn. Or simply take a cable car up to the Klein Matterhorn, a 12,700-foot outcropping that offers staggering views of the surrounding valleys.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Swiss Alps</location>
        <state>Switzerland</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Laden with glaciers, towering peaks, and flower-covered alpine valleys, the Swiss Alps are one of Europe's most scenic regions. Hike or bike the trails at Verbier, a legendary resort. Savor the alpine dusk at a summer street party in Zermatt, a mountain retreat that sits at the northern base of the Matterhorn. Or simply take a cable car up to the Klein Matterhorn, a 12,700-foot outcropping that offers staggering views of the surrounding valleys.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Northern Italy &amp; the Dolomites</region>
        <location>Northern Italy &amp; the Dolomites</location>
        <state>Northern Italy &amp; the Dolomites</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Dolomites are Italy's version of the Rockies. World-class winter and summer sports - including skiing, hiking, climbing, and river rafting - make these mountains a year-round playground for both Italians and visitors. Meander through winding, wildflower-filled valleys, and tackle the trails around Falcade by mountain bike. Or learn how to rock climb at Cortina d'Ampezzo, a high mountain town that offers activities for every type of explorer.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Austria</region>
        <location>Austria</location>
        <state>Austria</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Austria is a country of mountains - it's home to 56 peaks over 1,000 meters high. Hike through bucolic valleys beneath towering, glaciated peaks. Witness the spectacle of the Dachstein Ice Palace, an ice cave with sculptures and twisting passageways in the Dachstein Glacier. Or take a bus, car, or motorcycle across the Kaunertal Glacier Road, a stunning high alpine route connecting Austria with neighboring South Tyrol.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Lake Como</region>
        <location>Lake Como</location>
        <state>Lake Como</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Lake Como has been home to Italy's upper class for centuries. Embark on a boat tour of grand lakefront villas that date back to the 1500s. Visit the Villa del Balbianello, an immaculate residence with terraced gardens and a museum dedicated to its original owner, the explorer Guido Monzino. Or simply rent a sailboat and enjoy a picnic on the shimmering waters. You'll find you feel like royalty amid Lake Como's many pleasures.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Lake Maggiore</region>
        <location>Lake Maggiore</location>
        <state>Lake Maggiore</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Located in the foothills of the Dolomites, Lake Maggiore is Italy's second-largest lake and one of the country's most scenic destinations. Tour the Borromean Islands, a series of rocky islets that are home to ancient palazzos, chapels, and intricate gardens filled with citrus and olive trees. Looking for peace of mind? You'll find it in cobbled alleys and waterfront cafes of Isla dei Pescatori ("Fisherman's Island"), population 50.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</region>
        <location>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</location>
        <state>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Whether you prefer to walk through fields of wildflowers in an alpine meadow or test the limits of your climbing skills on a guided climb of Castle Mountain, Banff and Lake Louise have adventures for you. Plunge down rollicking, glacier-fed rivers on a rafting trip, take a helicopter flightseeing tour around towering peaks, or hop on an ATV for a four-wheeled excursion. It's simple: in Banff, fun rules the day.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Toronto</region>
        <location>Toronto</location>
        <state>Toronto</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Toronto sits on the shore of Lake Ontario, a hub of water sports and aquatic activities, including sailing, boating, canoeing, and kayaking. Spread your towel on the picturesque white beach of Sandbanks Provincial Park, home to the world's largest freshwater sandbar and dune system. Or take to the area's 90 kilometers of paved trails - perfect terrain for walkers, runners, and cyclists. After your day in the sun, Toronto's amenities await.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Jasper National Park</region>
        <location>Jasper National Park</location>
        <state>Jasper National Park</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Escape to Canada's largest Rocky Mountain park and explore 4,200 square miles of unspoiled sub-alpine and alpine terrain. Hike the 2-mile trail to Cavell Meadows and gaze in awe at the hanging Angel Glacier, perched on the precarious north face of Mt. Edith Cavell. Or drive the length of Icefields Parkway, a 143-mile scenic route that winds through mountains and glaciers - including the Columbia Icefield and the spectacular Crowfoot Glacier.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Niagara Falls</region>
        <location>Niagara Falls</location>
        <state>Niagara Falls</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Niagara Falls - 188 feet high and 2,200 feet across - were first successfully descended in 1901 by a 63-year-old woman in a barrel. But you don't need to risk your life to appreciate the physics of this stunning waterfall. Listen to the earth-shaking rumble of 4 million cubic feet of water pouring over the falls every minute. And for even more drama, don't miss the spectacular fireworks show that lights up the Falls after sunset.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Auckland</region>
        <location>Auckland</location>
        <state>Auckland</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Auckland's fervor for sailing is legendary - the harbor is so populated with racing boats that it's nicknamed the "City of Sails." Charter a sailboat for a day and sail to Motuihe Island, the perfect spot to anchor for lunch and a swim. Taste the signature chardonnays in the winemaking district of Matakana. Or relax in the geothermal pools at the Waiwera River. However you choose to recreate, Auckland provides the perfect retreat.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>French Alps</region>
        <location>French Alps</location>
        <state>French Alps</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The French Alps are home to three outstanding national parks: Vanoise, Ecrins, and Mercantour. Venture to Vanoise - France's oldest national park - and hike the high alpine trails near Val d'Isere. Raft, kayak, or canoe down churning whitewater on the region's many rivers. Ride a mountain bike across the high valleys of Chamonix, or, if you're feeling especially adventurous, learn how to skydive or paraglide at La Clusaz.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Oslo</region>
        <location>Oslo</location>
        <state>Oslo</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The splendidly verdant parks of Oslo make for perfect walks. Start at the riverside park at the Arkeselva River, which flows from Maridalsvannet Lake to Vaterland Park. Head to St. Hanshaugen, an urban park of tree-lined paths, streams, and cafes. Finally, explore the sculpture garden at Frogner Park, home to 212 bronze and granite sculptures made by Norway's own Gustav Vigeland. Don't forget your camera; the scenery in Oslo is incredible.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="4300" lat="46.010174" long="7.747029">
        <region>Salzburg</region>
        <location>Salzburg</location>
        <state>Salzburg</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Explore the Glaciers, see the Matterhorn]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Salzburg's setting is as visually remarkable as they come - the city sits on the banks of the Salzach River, nestled between the Kapuzinerberg and Monchsberg mountains. Ride a cable car to the 6,469-foot summit of the Untersberg, a nearby peak that provides dramatic mountain, city, and valley views. Or explore the many lakes, mountains, and forests of the Salzkammergut, a pastoral, unspoiled district just 10 miles east of the city.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="familyfun" reg="intl">
        <row locid="2734" lat="48.851961" long="2.360312">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Paris</location>
            <state>France</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Euro Disney]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Paris might be best known for romantic cafes and world-class museums, but the city has also made a name for itself as an amusement park mecca. Re-acquaint yourself with a familiar cast of characters at Disneyland&reg; Resort Paris, Europe's premier amusement park. Get your roller coaster fix at Parc Asterix, home the famous Thunder of Zeus ride. Or embark on a quest for aquatic nirvana at Aquaboulevard de Paris, the largest urban water park in Europe.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_Paris.png]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="4278" lat="55.730201" long="12.570064">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Copenhagen</location>
            <state>Denmark</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Tivoli Gardens]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Denmark's capital is home to two of the world's oldest amusement parks. Discover the Tunnel of Love and the Bakkens Hvile cabaret at Bakken Park, founded in 1583. Or bring the family to the historical grounds and classic roller coasters of Tivoli Gardens, which opened in 1843. Here, you can take a spin on the Rutsjebanen, a legendary wooden coaster built in 1914, or sail to the top of the Himmelskibet - the world's tallest carousel.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6053839" lat="25.121149" long="55.235757">
            <region>United Arab Emirates</region>
            <location>Dubai</location>
            <state>United Arab Emirates</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Ski Dubai]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[With its recent development of luxury hotels, golf courses, and upscale sports venues, Dubai has become known as the ultimate 21st century oasis. For example: Buckle your ski boots and prepare for schussing down 6,000 tons of snow at Ski Dubai, a 400-meter-tall indoor slope. Or, if you prefer water in liquid form, bring the kids to Wadi Wadi Water Park, a 12+-acre expanse of pools, water rides, and thrills that's only 20 minutes from the city center.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2793" lat="25.091387" long="-77.313535">
            <region>Caribbean</region>
            <location>Paradise Island</location>
            <state>Bahamas</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Atlantis resort properties]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Dive into one of nature's greatest theme parks: The Bahamas. Float, splash, and surf your way through the slides, rivers, and rapids of Aquaventure, a kid-friendly 63-acre waterscape on Paradise Island. Swim and interact with dolphins rescued from Hurricane Katrina. Boost your heart rate on the Stuart Cove Shark Adventure - a scuba dive that puts you face-to-face with docile Caribbean reef sharks - and wind down your day with a Mai Tai…on dry land, of course.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3927" lat="53.521951" long="-113.564375">
            <region>North America</region>
            <location>Edmonton</location>
            <state>Alberta</state>
            <site><![CDATA[There are over 800 stores and services]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Experience the West Edmonton Mall, home to more than 800 stores and services and 100 eateries. Here you'll find the world's largest indoor amusement park, with 24 rides and attractions. Whoop it up on the Mindbender - a triple-loop roller coaster - or skate like Gretzky on the NHL-size ice rink. Need to relax after all that adrenaline? Then head to the World Waterpark, a five-acre indoor waterscape that - you guessed it - is the largest in the world.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="179714" lat="40.383000" long="-3.729253">
            <region>Europe</region>
            <location>Madrid</location>
            <state>Spain</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Warner Brothers Movie World]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Venture to Madrid, Spain's sun-baked capital city, and experience some of the coolest amusement parks in Europe. Soar through the Spanish skies on Batman la Fuga ("Batman: the Ride") at Parque Warner Madrid, which offers a bevy of movie-themed rides. Cool off in the many pools and water rides at Aquapolis, Aqua Madrid, and Aqua Sur. Or take to the bumper boats, mini golf, and roller coasters at the kid-friendly Planeta Welby.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="182123" lat="22.259665" long="114.002680">
            <region>Asia</region>
            <location>Hong Kong</location>
            <state>China</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Ocean Park]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Hong Kong's attractions are myriad, but its amusement parks are near the top of the list. Discover the many wonders of Ocean Park, home to over 14 rides, a giant panda exhibit, and a four-story aquarium with sharks, jellyfish, and more. Pilot a Star Cruiser alongside Buzz Lightyear at Hong Kong Disneyland&reg;, a delight for the whole family. Or launch into orbit at the Space Museum, loaded with interactive exhibits for space fans of all ages.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="60083" lat="37.294031" long="-76.729609">
            <region>North America</region>
            <location>Montreal</location>
            <state>Quebec</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Biodome de Montreal]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Montreal's theme parks run the gamut from science to silliness. Learn about the four ecosystems of North America at Biodome de Montreal, a stunning tribute to nature's beauty. Explore the aquatic ecosystems of the nearby St. Lawrence River at the Biosphere, a towering geodesic dome that houses engaging, interactive exhibits. Finally, indulge your inner goofball with a trip to La Ronde Theme Park, home to nine world-class roller coasters.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6048265" lat="35.677500" long="139.768500">
            <region>Asia</region>
            <location>Tokyo</location>
            <state>Japan</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Tokyo Disneyland]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Among its many attractions, Tokyo is home to two Disney&reg;, theme parks and two additional family fun parks. Share the excitement of Pooh's Hunny Hunt with your entire family at Tokyo Disneyland&reg;. Journey to exotic ports of call at Tokyo DisneySea&reg;, a nautically-themed park that's loaded with thrilling rides and coasters. Then head to Tobu Zoo Park and LaQua for more coasters, Ferris wheels, and kids' rides than you can possibly handle in a day.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="179193" lat="34.677000" long="135.615500">
            <region>Asia</region>
            <location>Osaka</location>
            <state>Japan</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Universal Studios Japan]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Japan's second-largest city is home to Universal Studios&reg; Japan, the only Universal theme park located outside of the United States. Visit Peter Pan's Neverland, ogle prehistoric predators in Jurassic Park, and get your thrills on the Amazing Adventures of Spider-Man ride, a state-of-the-art tribute to Spidey. Then head into the city for a ride on the 350-foot-tall HEP 5 Ferris Wheel, which sits atop a department store.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="familyfun" reg="US">
      <row locid="2693" lat="28.483139" long="-81.377679">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Orlando</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Walt Disney World Resort]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Orlando, Florida is the epicenter of family-friendly attractions. Whether you're looking to treat the kids to the latest Walt Disney World&reg; rides or need a couples-only escape, you'll find no end of fun in the Sunshine State. Seeking thrills? Get your pulse racing with gravity-defying rides at Universal Orlando Resort&reg;. For amazing animal encounters, don't miss SeaWorld Orlando. Need to chill? A room awaits at one of the area's luxury resorts.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_orlando.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="5921" lat="33.830031" long="-117.9097">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Anaheim</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Knotts Berry Farm]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Anaheim put amusement parks on the map, with the grand opening of Disneyland&reg; Resort in 1955. If you haven't visited the home of Space Mountain and the Matterhorn in awhile, you'll be amazed at the new attractions. Take a journey to Disney's California Adventure&trade; park for a slew of new rides and family fun. And don't miss nearby Knott's Berry Farm and Six Flags Hurricane Harbor for kid-friendly coasters and all around good times.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_anaheim.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="9882" lat="41.425297" long="-82.695621">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Sandusky</location>
        <state>Ohio</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Cedar Point Amusement Park, Geuaga Lake Water Park]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Sandusky, Ohio is home to Cedar Point Amusement Park, where adventure seekers brave 69 of the world's most awesome rides, including 17 roller coasters. Enjoy delightful kid-friendly attractions or take on Millennium Force, a 310-foot high monster. When you're out of breath, cool off with the family at the 18-acre Soak City water park, cruise on Lake Erie, or spelunk local caverns in one of the area's many parks.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_sandusky.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2011" lat="34.005743" long="-118.34568">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Los Angeles</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Universal Studios Hollywood]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Get a taste of true Hollywood adventure in Los Angeles. Discover thrilling movie-themed rides and learn about filmmaking magic at Universal Studios&reg; Hollywood. Ride the antique carousel at Pacific Park on a pier in Santa Monica or hit Six Flags Magic Mountain for more fun for the whole family. And don't forget that Disneyland&reg; Resort and Knott's Berry Farm are just a short drive away.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_losangeles.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3077" lat="29.496934" long="-98.518113">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Antonio</location>
        <state>Texas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[SeaWorld San Antonio is the #1 destination theme park in Texas]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[For family-friendly amusement in the Lone Star state, look no farther than San Antonio. Check out some serious coasters at Six Flags Fiesta Texas, including Tony Hawk's Big Spin, which hurls riders along while spinning them 360 degrees. Encounter orcas and beluga whales and have a blast on unique rides for all ages at Sea World San Antonio. Not afraid to get wet? Ride the tubes and boogie board 'til you're soaked at Schlitterbahn Water Park.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_sanantonio.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3517" lat="28.006859" long="-82.452824">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Tampa</location>
        <state>Florida</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Busch Gardens Tampa Bay]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Tampa Bay is home to some of Florida's most adventurous attractions. Don't miss Africa-themed Busch Gardens, where you'll encounter live animal exhibits, interactive shows, roller coasters, and a three-story tree house. The region's most luxurious beaches beckon families yearning for sand and surf. In search of more wildlife? Tampa Bay's two National Wildlife Refuges are teeming with manatee, pelicans, and a variety of fish.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_tampa.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3073" lat="32.786977" long="-117.157818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Diego</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[SeaWorld San Diego]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Families flock to San Diego, where vacation memories are made at world-class attractions. The San Diego Zoo remains the zoo by which all others are measured, offering visitors encounters with rare species in their natural habitats. For bountiful fun for everyone, head to SeaWorld San Diego, Legoland California, or Knott's Soak City USA. Then take a trip to Belomont Park, where you'll find the famous "Big Dipper" wooden roller coaster.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_sandiego.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6296" lat="37.294031" long="-76.729609">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Williamsburg</location>
        <state>Virginia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Busch Gardens]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Have an adventure steeped in history in Williamsburg, Virgina. First stop, Busch Gardens, where old-world European charm meets state of the art roller coasters and family entertainment. Splash and play at Water Country USA, where you'll find 30 all-ages attractions. Or pay a visit to the Great Wolf Lodge, a family destination designed to capture the atmosphere and adventure of the north woods.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_williamsburg.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="829" lat="41.862949" long="-87.722415">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Chicago</location>
        <state>Illinois</state>
        <site><![CDATA[World Class museums]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Chicago's attractions are sure to delight the whole family. Start with Six Flags Great America; adventurous teens can test their mettle on high speed roller coasters while youngsters will enjoy family-friendly rides. Take a trip to the Shedd Aquarium to discover more than 700 species of dazzling marine animals. Then head to Lincoln Park Zoo for eye-to-eye encounters with gorillas, giraffes, and more - admission is free!]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_chicago.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8264" lat="35.797828" long="-83.565542">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Pigeon Forge</location>
        <state>Tennessee</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Dollywood]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Nestled in the Smoky Mountains of Tennessee, Pigeon Forge is home to the spectacular Dollywood amusement park, named after country music legend Dolly Parton. Spend your day enjoying family-friendly theme rides and exhibits highlighting the region's history and charm. Then cool off at Dollywood's Splash Country, the water park designed for all-ages fun. Hankering for more? Don't miss encounters with prehistoric beasts at the Dinosaur Walk Museum.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_pigeonforge.png]]></image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8264" lat="35.797828" long="-83.565542">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Minneapolis</location>
        <state>Minnesota</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Dollywood]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Minneapolis/St. Paul area is a big-time destination for travelers seeking amusement park fun. Start with the Mall of America, where the new Nickelodeon Universe and Underwater Adventures Aquarium turn lazy afternoons into adventures for all ages. And what about the mall's four stories of Lego displays? Cool! Then, grab your beach towels and venture to The Wisconsin Dells, appropriately known as the Water Park Capital of the World.]]></description>
        <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/promos/deals/tripfinder/amusement/amusement_pigeonforge.png]]></image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="golf" reg="intl">
      <row locid="4115" lat="50.117215" long="-122.969467">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Whistler</location>
        <state>British Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Four championship courses.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Tee up amid some of the West's best mountain scenery in Whistler, B.C. This outdoor-lover's getaway is best known for its world-class ski terrain, but Whistler Valley has become a premier destination for golfers of all ages and abilities. All four of Whistler's championship courses have junior tees - perfect for the entire family. Plus, kids ages 10 to 18 play for free on Whistler Village's three courses.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="500691" lat="20.746455" long="-105.371468">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Vallarta</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Vista Vallarta]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Puerto Vallarta's courses rank among some of Mexico's finest. Vista Vallarta, a Jack Nicklaus course, offers sweeping views of Puerto Vallarta and the ocean beyond. Head to the links at Punta Mita, the Monterey Peninsula of Mexico. (The Four Seasons Punta Mita has eight oceanfront holes, with one on an island in the Pacific.) Or choose Paradise Village's "El Tigre" course, a challenging loop with a live - and securely encaged - Bengal tiger.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="935" lat="21.095766" long="-86.818376">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Riviera Maya</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Fairmont Mayakoba]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Take to the lush courses of the Riviera Maya and discover why Mexico is the second most popular destination for American golfers. Play El Camaleón, a Greg Norman-designed course that hosted Mexico's first PGA Tour event in 2007. (Be prepared for the 15th hole, a seaside par 3 that plays directly toward the Caribbean.) And don't miss the remarkable Golf Club of Playacar, which incorporates over 200 Mayan ruins into its twisting, jungle-lined layout.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="181118" lat="32.379348" long="-64.681619">
        <region>Caribbean</region>
        <location>St. George</location>
        <state>Bermuda</state>
        <site><![CDATA[There are 9 Bermuda golf courses.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Bermuda may be small in size, but with nine courses on the island, it has the world's highest concentration of golf per square mile. Tee off at the Fairmont Southampton Hotel, a Theodore Robinson-designed course that features some of the largest elevation changes of any course in the world - the first two holes boast a vertical drop of more than 200 feet. Feeling rusty? Warm up at the expansive Bermuda Golf Academy's driving range and putting greens.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1820" lat="17.998446" long="-76.791803">
        <region>Caribbean</region>
        <location>Kingston</location>
        <state>Jamica</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Half Moon Golf Course]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Start your Jamaican golf adventure at Half Moon Golf Course, a member of the Jack Nicklaus "Great Golf Resorts of the World." Designed by Robert Trent Jones, Sr., Half Moon features amenities for both beginner and advanced golfers, including undulating greens, sculpted bunkers, and multiple tee boxes. Then visit Manchester Club, the Caribbean's oldest course, or head to the Tryall Club, a demanding course that's as luxurious as they come.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6023729" lat="56.325966" long="-2.787227">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>St. Andrews</location>
        <state>Scotland</state>
        <site><![CDATA[St. Andrews]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Every true devotee of the game must undertake a pilgrimage to Scotland, the birthplace of golf. Grant your own wish and play a round (or three) at the Royal and Ancient Golf Club of St. Andrews, the world's most revered set of links. Venture to Carnoustie, an equally prestigious course that has hosted numerous British Open championships, or take to the links at Muirfield, another Scottish classic.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="182570" lat="51.296002" long="-0.327236">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Surrey</location>
        <state>England</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Surrey contains over 100 golf clubs.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Surrey County, a lovely, pastoral district of farms and villages, is located one hour southwest of London. It's also home to over 100 well known golf courses and clubs, making it a European destination for hackers and low-handicappers alike. Start your golfing adventure at the splendid links at Abbey Moor. Then head to Worpleson Golf Club, Surrey's mix of challenging and forgiving courses designed to please golfers of all skill levels.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="181451" lat="52.096115" long="-9.816442">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Kerry</location>
        <state>Ireland</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Ballybunion Golf course.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Escape to the rolling, emerald pastures and rocky coastlines of County Kerry, Ireland's premier golf destination. Book a tee time at the world-famous Ballybunion Golf Club, and play one of two seaside courses laden with dunes, shore grasses, and incredible views. Or choose from three courses at Killarney Golf Club, all nestled on the shores of the Killarney Lakes at the foot of Macgillycuddy Reeks, Ireland's highest mountain range.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1384" lat="37.183263" long="-3.608943">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Andalucia</location>
        <state>Spain</state>
        <site><![CDATA[300 days of sunshine.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Andalusia, Spain's southernmost region, is a golfer's paradise with top-notch courses bathed in sunshine over 300 days a year. Play your way through Marbella, the Mediterranean district that boasts such famous courses as La Quinta and Robert Trent Jones Sr.-designed Las Brisas. Continue to Costa de la Luz, where the magnificent Jack Nicklaus-designed Montecastillo Golf Club draws links enthusiasts from around the globe.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="9631" lat="22.924199" long="-109.87511">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Los Cabos</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[PGA Senior Slam Tournament]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[If the surf, sand, and near-constant sunshine of Los Cabos aren't enough to entertain you, hit the links at one of the area's great courses. Don't miss Palmilla, a five-star resort with 27 holes designed by Jack Nicklaus, and Cabo Real Golf Club, with oceanview holes that entice experts and beginners alike. Look out for the pros: Cabo has hosted the Senior Slam tourney for many years, attracting golf greats such as Raymond Floyd and Hale Irwin.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="golf" reg="US">
        <row locid="2790" lat="33.440588" long="-112.010344">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Phoenix</location>
            <state>Arizona</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Home to more than 200 golf courses.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[There's a reason the National Golf Foundation named Greater Phoenix the "Golf Capitol of the World." Start with over 200 courses set amid the red rock bluffs and saguaro cacti. Be sure to visit the courses designed by the pros - Robert Trent Jones, Jack Nicklaus, and Arnold Palmer all have fairways here. What's more, you'll enjoy your day (or week, or why not make it a month?) of golf with all the amenities of luxurious spa resorts.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2790" lat="33.440588" long="-112.010344">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Oahu</location>
            <state>Hawaii</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Home to more than 200 golf courses.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Wherever you tee up on Oahu, you're surrounded by breathtaking tropical scenery. Take your pick of more than forty public and private courses, from casual municipal links to luxurious resorts with all the amenities. Hit fairways on bluffs with the Pacific Ocean crashing on rocks below. Oahu offers more courses than any other Hawaiian island, making it a true golfer's paradise. It's many other kinds of paradise, too.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2790" lat="33.440588" long="-112.010344">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Maui</location>
            <state>Hawaii</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Home to more than 200 golf courses.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Try your hardest to keep your eye on the ball when you're golfing on Maui. Here you'll enjoy fairways abutting ancient lava floes, palm groves, and rainbows in the ocean mist. Tee up at any of 16 courses, many of them ranked at or near the top of "world's best" lists. After all, this is the island where the PGA Tour's Mercedes Benz Championship is held every year, luring the pros to one of earth's most breathtaking settings.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2693" lat="28.483139" long="-81.377679">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Orlando</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[176 golf courses within an hour's drive of Orlando.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Tired of checking the weather report every time you want to hit the fairway? Journey to Orlando, where the sun shines 300 days of year on 176 courses within an hour of the city. Over twenty golf academies make this a serious town for links, and all the attention to design and natural beauty is apparent in every sculpted green. And why not take in some of the area's famous attractions - from theme parks to beaches - on your off day?]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2742" lat="26.706729" long="-80.101839">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Palm Beach</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Palm Beach County is known as Florida's Golf Capital]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Over 160 courses greet visitors to Palm Beach, known as Florida's Golf Capital. Hit the links at some of the country's oldest courses, even the one where the classic comedy Caddyshack was filmed. Work on improving your handicap among sand traps and water features designed to complement the natural beauty of one of America's most lush regions. Venture to Palm Beach to play in the shadows of the greats.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2491" lat="33.737337" long="-78.895569">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Myrtle Beach</location>
            <state>South Carolina</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Brunswick Islands]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach, South Carolina offers links enthusiasts more than a hundred of the country's highest rated courses. Affordable gems and elegant greens designed by the likes of Arnold Palmer, Reese Jones, and Dan Maples greet golfers looking to improve their game. Enjoy some laid back, lemonade-sipping golf at courses nestled amid mossy oaks. Bringing the kids along? Make memories at any of the area's 46 fun-themed kids' courses.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2491" lat="33.737337" long="-78.895569">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Ft. Myers</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Brunswick Islands]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Nestled on the Caloosahatchee River, Ft. Myers, Florida was the vacation getaway of Henry Ford and Thomas Edison. But you don't have to be a wealthy industrialist to enjoy the area's wealth of courses. Improve your game at any number of courses geared toward the average golfer, or tee up on links worthy of the pros. After some quality time with your nine iron, kick back at one of many superb eateries on the downtown waterfront.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="460" lat="30.358724" long="-97.805189">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Austin</location>
            <state>Texas</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Recently rated the nation's number 1 golf city by CNN.com]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Offering 51 public courses within a 30-mile radius, Austin, Texas welcomes golfers of all skill levels. Try out your new putter on one of four nationally ranked championship courses at Barton Creek Resort and Spa. Reserve your tee time at the popular Lions Municipal Golf Course, a set of public greens rich in history. Whatever your handicap, you'll see why CNN rated Austin the nation's #1 golf city.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2885" lat="33.843378" long="-116.539483">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Palm Springs</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Cathedral Canyon Country Club.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[For sheer beauty and an abundance of challenging courses, Palm Springs raises the bar. Perfect your swing with the San Jacinto Mountains as your backdrop at the spectacular Cathedral Canyon Country Club. See for yourself why Cimarron Golf Resort was chosen as one of Golf Digest's Best Places to Play. And don't miss the affordable Indian Springs Country Club, which was a hit within the first year it opened. Palm Springs means serious golf.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3073" lat="32.786977" long="-117.157818">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>San Diego</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Try out Torrey Pines]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Try out Torrey Pines - The prestigious 2008 U.S. Open will be held at the internationally renowned Torrey Pines Golf Course.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2417" lat="36.595308" long="-121.877830">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Monterey</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Pebble Beach Resorts]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Home to both the famous Pebble Beach Golf Links and the oldest course west of the Mississippi, Monterey, California offers golfers a combined 471 holes at 20 public and private courses. Plan your golf adventure around a trip up scenic Highway 68 to the courses of sun-drenched Carmel Valley. You'll tee off amid the splendor of California's sea-splashed coastline and find out why avid golfers make pilgrimages to this land of fair weather fairways.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif]]></image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="spas" reg="intl">
       <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Whistler</region>
        <location>Whistler</location>
        <state>Whistler</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Book a spa treatment and give your body a much-needed rest from Whistler's nonstop skiing, hiking, biking, and golfing. This mega-resort town boasts more than 20 spas offering everything from Moor Mud wraps to Ayurvedic facials. Treat your toes to a pedicure while a stylist works magic on your hair. And gentlemen, listen up: many spas in Whistler offer special rates for couples, making a shiatsu massage for two the perfect surprise gift.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</region>
        <location>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</location>
        <state>Banff &amp; Lake Louise</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[While many travelers flock to Banff and Lake Louise for the multitude of outdoor activities, a growing number of visitors love the area for its spas, salons, and hot springs. Indulge yourself with a Vichy hydrotherapy treatment or a full body Swedish massage session. Or take the whole family to one of Banff's hot springs complexes, both of which have thermal pools, swimming pools, cafes, and children's play areas.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Bahamas</region>
        <location>Bahamas</location>
        <state>Bahamas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Bahamas are home to some of the world's most exclusive spas, including the five-star One & Only Ocean Club, where you can enjoy a heated seaweed mask followed by a massage. Book a stay for two at the Sandals Royal Bahamian Resort & Spa, a couples-only escape with eucalyptus steam baths and hot and cold plunge pools. You'll find pampering the top priority at every resort on this tropical isle.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Dominican Republic</region>
        <location>Dominican Republic</location>
        <state>Dominican Republic</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Thanks to boutique resorts like the Sivory Punta Cana - a beachfront enclave with Balinese suites and three top-tier restaurants - the Dominican Republic is quickly becoming known as a luxury destination. Enjoy a beachfront shiatsu massage at an all-inclusive resort and spa, or book a hot volcanic stone massage at Puerto Plata's new Maxim Bungalow, which also offers caviar facials. Luxury is no stranger to this island paradise.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>St. Lucia</region>
        <location>St. Lucia</location>
        <state>St. Lucia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[St. Lucia is an island of sublime luxury resorts. Lounge beside your cabana and private infinity pool at Jade Mountain resort, which overlooks the Pitons and the Caribbean. Unwind in the luxurious isolation of Anse Chastanet, a 600-acre resort with private cabanas and a beachfront spa offering Swedish massage and aromatherapy. Whether you prefer air conditioning or fresh air, St. Lucia has a luxurious retreat for you.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Jamaica</region>
        <location>Jamaica</location>
        <state>Jamaica</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Jamaica is resplendent with a variety of high-end spas and resorts, including Goldeneye, the 18-acre luxury resort that was once the estate of <em>James Bond</em> author Ian Fleming. Discover the remarkable Caves resort, an oceanfront escape with sea caves, grottos, and ten private cottages. Or treat your family to hot stone massages, Frette linens, and butler service at the Ritz Carlton Rose Hall, a five-star resort set on 5,000 acres.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Cancun</region>
        <location>Cancun</location>
        <state>Cancun</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Canc&uacute;n's resorts and spas rank among the finest in the world. Proof: the JW Marriott Canc&uacute;n was rated one of the world's top 50 resort spas by Conde Nast. Immerse yourself in a cascading waterfall massage at Le Meridien Canc&uacute;n, a French-themed spa with private pools and Swiss showers. Traveling as a twosome? Treat your significant other to a private outdoor massage suite at the Le Blanc Spa, where shiatsu, Thai, and Swedish massage experts await.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Los Cabos</region>
        <location>Los Cabos</location>
        <state>Los Cabos</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Slip away to Los Cabos, home of Mexico's most posh spas and hotels. Splurge on an algae body wrap at Las Ventanas Al Paraiso, Cabo's most luxurious retreat. Receive an innovative wine- and grape-infused skin treatment at the SOMMA Wine Spa. And stay in boutique heaven at the Casa del Mar beach resort, home to a silent sunbathing area and nightly holistic meditation rituals around a beach fire. When luxury calls, Los Cabos answers.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Vallarta</region>
        <location>Vallarta</location>
        <state>Vallarta</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Pacific coastline north of Puerto Vallarta is home to a wealth of upscale resorts - so many, in fact, that it's known as the "Mexican Riviera." Revel in an exfoliating chamomile body scrub at the Apuane Spa, located in the Four Seasons Punta Mita. Or relax beside the sprawling pool complex at Grand Velas, a five-star resort with an on-site spa that offers a hot and cold lagoon, Swiss showers, and a full massage menu.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Barbados</region>
        <location>Barbados</location>
        <state>Barbados</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Barbados is a heavenly getaway for romantics, single travelers, and families alike. Bring your clubs to Sandy Lane Resort, where the golf courses and spa are equally renowned. Relax with the family beside the expansive, multi-tiered pool complex at the historical Crane Resort, built in 1887. But bring only your spouse to The House, a four-star, adults-only resort where each couple is assigned a personal ambassador.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
       <destinations category="historical" reg="intl">
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>Paris</region>
        <location>Paris</location>
        <state>Paris</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Paris's history is as rich as its cuisine. Experience the towering nave and flying buttresses of Notre Dame de Paris cathedral, one of the grandest buildings in Europe. Savor the views of Paris from the observation deck of the Eiffel Tower, perhaps the world's most recognizable structure. Art aficionados, head for the Monet and Renoir collections at the Musee d'Orsay and don't forget to trade a smile with Mona Lisa at the Louvre.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2786" lat="39.992618" long="-75.148994">
        <region>Rome</region>
        <location>Rome</location>
        <state>Rome</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Birthplace of independence: Liberty Bell, Independence Hall, Betsy Ross House.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Begin your tour of Rome's historical attractions with a visit to Vatican City and St. Peter's Basilica, a place of pilgrimage for Catholics from around the globe. Witness the spectacle that is the Roman Coliseum, built in 70 AD, and the towering columns of the Pantheon (built 125 AD). Then toss a coin into the famous Trevi Fountain and continue to the Musei Vaticani, a series of Vatican museums that includes the world-renowned Sistine Chapel.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3763" lat="38.899239" long="-77.041615">
        <region>Jerusalem</region>
        <location>Jerusalem</location>
        <state>Jerusalem</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the monuments.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Jerusalem is one of the world's holiest cities; its unique history, spiritual significance, and cultural palette make it an exceptional destination. Explore the Old City - the historical city center that's divided into the Armenian, Jewish, Christian, and Muslim Quarters. View legendary religious sites, including Temple Mount and the Western Wall. Or simply stroll the narrow streets lined with savory food stalls and craft shops.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6296" lat="37.294031" long="-76.729609">
        <region>Florence</region>
        <location>Florence</location>
        <state>Florence</state>
        <site><![CDATA[College of William and Mary]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The gorgeous city of Florence, capital of Tuscany and birthplace of the Italian Renaissance, beckons the learned and curious. Discover the majesty of David, one of Michelangelo's most famous statues. Admire the famed Cupola del Duomo, a domed structure atop the Basilica di Santa Maria di Fiore, built in 1436. Or spend an afternoon in the presence of seminal works of the Renaissance in the many galleries at Galleria dell'Accademia.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="637" lat="36.166226" long="-86.74206">
        <region>London</region>
        <location>London</location>
        <state>London</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Grand Ole Opry]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[London's cultural resume ranks among the best in the world. (It is, after all, the city that gave birth to the English Renaissance, the Industrial Revolution, and the Gothic Revival.) For starters, visit London's four UNESCO World Heritage Sites: the Palace of Westminster, the Tower of London, the historical settlement of Greenwich, and the Royal Botanic Gardens at Kew. Or discover the modern charms of Fleet Street, West End, or Hyde Park.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3077" lat="29.496934" long="-98.518113">
        <region>Cancun</region>
        <location>Cancun</location>
        <state>Cancun</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Alamo]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Surrounded by a treasure trove of Mayan ruins and historical sites, Canc&uacute;n sits at the intersection of modernity and history. Take a day trip to the awe-inspiring ruins at Chichen Itza before returning to your posh beachfront hotel. Venture further afield to Chetumal, where the Museum of Mayan Culture awaits. Or stay in town and visit the Casa de la Cultura Museum, home to native artworks, traditional dances, theater events, and music performances.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3079" lat="32.090243" long="-81.164637">
        <region>Athens</region>
        <location>Athens</location>
        <state>Athens</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Georgia's first city.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Founded more than 3,000 years ago, Athens is one of the world's oldest cities. Journey to the Acropolis, where collections of artifacts from the Temple of Athena, the Parthenon, and the Theatre of Dionysus await. Visit the awe-inspiring Ancient Agora of Athens, a temple dedicated to the Greek gods built in the 5th century. Or discover the Benaki Museum, a downtown institution that houses a vast range of Greek art, from prehistoric to modern.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="833" lat="32.82358" long="-79.994309">
        <region>Beijing</region>
        <location>Beijing</location>
        <state>Beijing</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums and landmarks]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Travel to the heart of China's rich cultural traditions: Beijing. Experience the grandeur of the Great Wall, the 4,000-mile fortification that defined the northern boundary of successive Chinese dynasties. Marvel at the intricate palaces, guard towers, and gates of Beijing's Forbidden City, built in 1420. And don't miss Tiananmen Square, the sprawling central plaza that has been the site of some of China's most significant cultural uprisings.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>Istanbul</region>
        <location>Istanbul</location>
        <state>Istanbul</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The world's only metropolis situated on two continents, Istanbul straddles the Bosphorous Strait, that divides Europe and Asia. Discover the wonders of this unique cultural blend. Start at the ornate courtyards of the Topkapi Palace and explore the Underground Cistern, a sprawling cavern filled with Roman arches, columns, and shimmering waters. Or witness the massive, Byzantine dome of the Hagia Sophia museum, built in the 8th century.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>Lima</region>
        <location>Lima</location>
        <state>Lima</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Lima is often known as the first stop on the journey to the miraculous ruins at Machu Picchu, one of the seven wonders of the world. But the city has plenty of attractions within its borders - start with the Cercado de Lima, the historical central district that's a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Explore the neighborhood's colonial architecture or haggle with artisans who set up shop along winding streets that are themselves a feast for the senses.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>Prague</region>
        <location>Prague</location>
        <state>Prague</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Ornate and steeped in history, Prague is one of Europe's most gorgeous cities. Visit the massive Prague Castle - the world's largest ancient castle - and walk the narrow, shop-lined streets of the Old Town before crossing the 15th century Charles Bridge. Peruse the Strahov Monastery, a museum and library built in 1120, and syncronize your watch to the Prague Astronomical Clock, a medieval timepiece mounted on a tower in the Old Town.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>Quebec City</region>
        <location>Quebec City</location>
        <state>Quebec City</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Quebec, Canada's second-oldest existing European settlement, celebrates its 400th anniversary in 2008. Explore the massive stone ramparts and battlements in the Old City - the oldest still-standing fortifications north of Mexico. Visit the endlessly engaging Musee de la Civilisation, home to interactive exhibits on Canadian history and humanities. And drop in on the grand Chateau Frontenac hotel for exquisitely-presented afternoon tea.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>Bangkok</region>
        <location>Bangkok</location>
        <state>Bangkok</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[For an energetic introduction to Southeast Asian culture, venture to Bangkok, the bustling capital of Thailand. Tour the Wat Arun ("Temple of the Dawn"), a towering Buddhist temple that features an unmistakable central spire. Meander through the manicured grounds and gold-plated spires of the Grand Palace, home to Thai kings until the mid-20th century. Or take a day tour to the historic ruins of Ayudhaya, this vibrant country's former capital.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="historical" reg="US">
      <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Boston</location>
        <state>Massachusetts</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[There's no better place to explore America's past than Boston. Start with a walk on the Freedom Trail past sites of epic Revolutionary War struggles. Visit the city's oldest residence - Paul Revere's 1680 home and the site where his midnight ride began. Looking for a more contemporary experience? The museums in Boston are an embarrassment of riches; don't miss the Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Children's Museum, and New England Aquarium.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2786" lat="39.992618" long="-75.148994">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Philadelphia</location>
        <state>Pennsylvania</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Birthplace of independence: Liberty Bell, Independence Hall, Betsy Ross House.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The birthplace of independence provides ample chances to discover American history. Explore Philadelphia's many historical landmarks, including Independence Hall, Betsy Ross's house, and the iconic Liberty Bell. Spend the day absorbing art and history in the city's superb museums, including the Philadelphia Museum of Art and the Franklin Institute. Love architecture? Don't miss the marvelous Society Hill and Rittenhouse Square neighborhoods.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3763" lat="38.899239" long="-77.041615">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Washington DC</location>
        <state>District of Columbia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the monuments.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Washington, D.C. is monumental in every sense of the word. Embark on a quest to the nation's capital and experience the grandeur of the Washington Monument and the solemnity of the Vietnam Memorial, all a stone's throw from the halls of power. Watch democracy in action in the U.S. Capitol Building, marvel at the Smithsonian's free exhibits, and spend the afternoon among the stacks in the Library of Congress. This is the city where history is made.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6296" lat="37.294031" long="-76.729609">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Williamsburg</location>
        <state>Virginia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[College of William and Mary]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Williamsburg, Virginia astounds visitors with its hands-on approach to history. Kids love to learn at Colonial Williamsburg, the amusement park where America's founding comes to life. Walk in the footsteps of the nation's earliest scholars at William and Mary, the country's second oldest college. Have a passion for military history? You can stand in the very place where George Washington defeated General Cornwallis in Yorktown.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="637" lat="36.166226" long="-86.74206">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Nashville</location>
        <state>Tennessee</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Grand Ole Opry]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Nashville, Tennessee is rightly famous as America's mecca for country music. Step into the Grand Ole Opry and catch today's rising stars as well as the giants of country music's recent past. Then saunter on over to the Ryman Auditorium and the Country Music Hall of Fame for more music and artifacts. It's not all about the music, though. Civil War buffs will love exploring the historical site of the Battle of Nashville.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3077" lat="29.496934" long="-98.518113">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>San Antonio</location>
        <state>Texas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[The Alamo]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Remember the Alamo when you're thinking of a cultural adventure. San Antonio is the site of the famous fort, but there's much more to see in this city deep in the heart of Texas. Spend an afternoon among the San Antonio Missions, the largest concentration of missions in North America. Hop over to La Vita Historical Arts Village, the city's oldest neighborhood, now an artists' enclave. This is a city where you can get happily lost in history.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3079" lat="32.090243" long="-81.164637">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Savannah</location>
        <state>Georgia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Georgia's first city.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Life moves at a more leisurely pace in genteel Savannah. Explore Georgia's first city, where more than 45 elegant inns and B&Bs define southern hospitality. If you're inspired by beautiful buildings, you'll want to head straight for the city's historical district, where you'll see eight distinct architectural styles on grand display. Or venture to the Wormsloe plantation or the stately Mercer House for a glimpse of true southern style.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="833" lat="32.82358" long="-79.994309">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Charleston</location>
        <state>South Carolina</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Museums and landmarks]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[One of America's best-preserved cities, Charleston, South Carolina exudes historical charm. Journey down cobblestone streets past grand mansions, magnificent churches, and lush gardens, all meticulously maintained. Explore the history of the Old South with plantation tours or visits to numerous museums dedicated to the Civil War. Once you've been steeped in heritage, downtown Charleston offers fine southern dining for the hungry history buff.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Mackinac Island</location>
        <state>Michigan</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Mackinac Island is one of Michigan's most charming Victorian escapes. Here, motorized vehicles of any kind are banned, so you'll explore this relaxing landscape by horse drawn carriage or tandem bike. Discover the fascinating artifacts of Native, military, and missionary cultures who have called the island home. Or, marvel at either of two butterfly attractions, just examples of the many natural wonders you'll encounter at this island getaway.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Santa Fe</location>
        <state>New Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Stunning Native American art meets Spanish architecture in Santa Fe, North America's oldest capital city. Start at the plaza, the city's cultural hub. Get your creative juices flowing with visits to the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum and the Museum of International Folk Art. Looking for history as well as art? Step back into the 19th-century at the meticulously presented Rancho de las Golondrinas or the elegant Palace of the Governors.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="hotspots" reg="allinclusive">
        <row locid="935" lat="21.095766" long="-86.818376">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Cancun</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[See a show!]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[If you want to experience the legendary beaches, ruins, and nightlife of Mexico, then escape to Canc&uacute;n. Discover the awe-inspiring intelligence of dolphins during a safe, intimate swim with these fascinating marine mammals. Or simply indulge yourself with a beachside massage at one of Canc&uacute;n's many all-inclusive four- and five-star resorts, where stress disappears as quickly as you can order your next poolside beverage.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="660" lat="42.343488" long="-71.047244">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Riviera Maya</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum).]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Journey to the sun-soaked heart of the Yucatan Peninsula, where you'll enjoy easy access to the Mayan ruins of Chichen It'za and Tulum. Escape to the eco-conscious Xcaret Eco Theme Park for an inspiring adventure composed of equal parts conservation, Mayan culture, and snorkeling. Then recharge your batteries on the area's vast, unspoiled beaches and all-inclusive resorts. However you choose to worship the sun, Riviera Maya is your temple.]]></description>
            <image><![CDATA[http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif]]></image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2786" lat="39.992618" long="-75.148994">
            <region>Dominican Republic</region>
            <location>Dominican Republic</location>
            <state>Dominican Republic</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Museums (Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum, Aquarium, Childrens Museum]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Located on the island of Hispaniola, the Dominican Republic is home to the Caribbean's highest mountain, Pico Duarte. With some of the best hiking trails in the region, you can easily explore the lush scenery on foot. Or by boat - check out over 800 miles of pristine beaches and vibrant coral reefs. But the DR isn't all charmingly rustic; the country has a host of all-inclusive resorts specializing in pampering the most discerning luxury traveler.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3763" lat="38.899239" long="-77.041615">
            <region>Jamaica</region>
            <location>Jamaica</location>
            <state>Jamaica</state>
            <site><![CDATA[College of William and Mary.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Venture to the idyllic, sugar-sand beaches and verdant jungles of Jamaica, the birthplace of the all-inclusive resort. Explore the underwater shipwrecks, reefs, and rock formations that make this Caribbean island a premier diving and snorkeling destination. Glide through the forest canopy on a zip line tour, or sip a mango-infused cocktail under a thatched umbrella at a spa resort. Whatever your pleasure, Jamaica is the place to unwind.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6296" lat="37.294031" long="-76.729609">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Puerto Vallarta</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[College of William and Mary]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Looking for an artsy, natural escape from the rigors of everyday life? Consider Puerto Vallarta, renowned for its resident artists and potters, chic boutiques, and bustling music venues. Get an adrenaline fix in the nearby Sierra Madre Mountains, where canopy tours, jeep safaris, and canyoneering adventures await. Then complete your coastal getaway with a whale-watching cruise; gray whales are common here from January through late spring. ]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="637" lat="36.166226" long="-86.74206">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Los Cabos</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Grand Ole Opry]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Commune with the Pacific Ocean at Los Cabos, a beach destination that offers equal servings of adventure (including sport fishing, whale-watching, and surfing) and relaxation (thanks to beachfront spa treatments, glorious nightly sunsets, and an excellent dining scene). Expand your knowledge of the local environment with an ecotour - by kayak, sailboat, or simply a stroll on the beach. However you define bliss, you'll achieve it in Los Cabos.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3077" lat="29.496934" long="-98.518113">
            <region>St. Lucia</region>
            <location>St. Lucia</location>
            <state>St. Lucia</state>
            <site><![CDATA[The Alamo]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Voyage to St. Lucia, the Caribbean's hidden gem. Discover the island's 19,000 acres of lush rainforest, home to the Mangrove Cuckoo and the St. Lucian Parrot. Bicycle through gentle forest paths or paddle a sea kayak along the base of the breathtaking Pitons, a pair of peaks that rise more than 2,400 feet above the ocean. Or rejuvenate your mind and body with a Caribbean sea wrap at one of St. Lucia's renowned luxury resorts.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3079" lat="32.090243" long="-81.164637">
            <region>Antigua</region>
            <location>Antigua</location>
            <state>Antigua</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Georgia's first city.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[If it's beaches you seek - glorious, sunny, life-giving beaches - look no further than Antigua. This Caribbean hotspot has 365 of them - one for each day of the year. Relax in an oceanfront villa (with butler service, of course) at one of Antigua's all-inclusive resorts. Or mingle with the nautical set on the piers of this sailing-obsessed isle. After you've experienced Antigua's hospitality and luminous natural beauty, you'll want to stay year-round.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="833" lat="32.82358" long="-79.994309">
            <region>Mexico</region>
            <location>Cozumel</location>
            <state>Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Museums and landmarks]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Immerse yourself in the crystalline waters, expansive coral reefs, and pristine beaches of Cozumel, one of the world's top diving destinations. Snorkel, dine, and sunbathe the day away at Chankanaab Park, a sheltered lagoon with snorkel-friendly reefs, a botanical garden, and beachfront cantinas. Or, if it's pure relaxation that you're after, enjoy a hot stone massage or poolside cocktail at one of the island's many all-inclusive resorts.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="8308" lat="45.865078" long="-84.631197">
            <region>Costa Rica</region>
            <location>Costa Rica</location>
            <state>Costa Rica</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Tour the island on a tandem bicycle.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Venture to the lush mountains and endless beaches of Costa Rica, the birthplace of the ecotourism movement. Discover the country's spectacular biodiversity, including howler monkeys, toucans, and humpback whales. Thanks to Costa Rica's varied topography and small size, you can take a canopy tour in a cloud forest, climb the flanks of an active volcano, and enjoy a Pacific Ocean sunset on a stunning beach - all in the same day.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="outdoors" reg="US">
          <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Boise</location>
        <state>Idaho</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The snow-capped Rocky Mountains set the stage for outdoor adventures in Boise, Idaho. Explore 2,600 acres of natural beauty any time of year at Bogus Basin Ski Resort. If ATVs and dirt bikes get your motor running, you'll have plenty of muddy trails to rip through. Or rent a kayak and spend the day on the Boise River. Whether it's biking, hiking, or just breathing fresh mountain air, you'll find plenty to do in this Southwest Idaho escape.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Snowmass/Aspen</location>
        <state>Colorado</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Four mountains. Two scenic towns. Welcome to Aspen and Snowmass! Pack a picnic lunch and hike to fields of wildflowers. Hop on a horse or mountain bike and trek on trails winding through untouched wilderness. Traveling with kids? They'll squeal with delight playing on the Eurobungy trampoline. But before you leave these charming alpine towns, don't forget to take a nature walk guided by one of the area's resident experts.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Vail</location>
        <state>Colorado</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Vail is the nation's hippest resort town and a magnet for celebrities looking for a little R&R. It's not hard to see why, with golf, horseback riding, rock climbing, and kayaking being just a few of the ways visitors can enjoy the splendor of this magnificent mountain town. Grab a gondola to Vail Mountain's Adventure Ridge or take the kids up in a balloon ride. Then take to the trails on your bike. At days end, Vail offers exciting nightlife.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Sunriver/Bend</location>
        <state>Oregon</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Oregon's Bend and Sunriver are perfect places to experience the splendor of the Cascade Mountain range. Hit nearly 40 miles of paved bike and walking paths, or dip your paddle into the glasslike surface of a serene mountain lake. Don't worry if you left your horse at home - stables staffed with friendly guides will meet your equestrian needs. Outdoor fun for the whole family awaits in these charming mountain towns.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Big Sky</location>
        <state>Montana</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[They don't call it Big Sky for nothing. The sweeping vistas of this Montana getaway are enough to make even the most seasoned outdoors enthusiast swoon. Take the year-round ski lift up Lone Mountain to a tangled network of trails. Marvel at miles of back country scenery by mountain bike or bring your rod and reel for some of Montana's famous fly-fishing. Whether you're looking for biking or bison, Big Sky provides adventure in a big way.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Salt Lake City</location>
        <state>Utah</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Lush forests, deep canyons, and North America's saltiest lake lure outdoor adventurers to - where else? - Salt Lake City. Use the city as your base camp for excursions by horseback, mountain bike, or your trusty pair of boots. Explore parks just minutes from the city center or soar above it all in a hot air balloon. For climbing, you can't go wrong in the grand Wasatch Mountains. This site of the winter Olympics guarantees great memories.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Stowe</location>
        <state>Vermont</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Four seasons a year, Stowe, Vermont means serious outdoor recreation, especially if you're a trail lover. Panoramic views reward your efforts as you hike scenic Mount Mansfield. Enjoy the greenery in over 3,000 acres of wilds preserved by the Stowe Land Trust. Warm weather visitors often spend one day hiking the winding trails and the next unwinding in the more than 50 hotels and resorts, 50 restaurants, and 70 unique boutique and specialty shops.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Sun Valley</location>
        <state>Idaho</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Sun Valley's Bald Mountain is sort of a misnomer - this outdoor getaway is covered with fields of wildflowers. Wear out your boots on 28 miles of trails on "Baldy" for sure, but don't miss Silver Creek, where you can try your hand at fly-fishing. Ride the rapids on Salmon River or tee off at award-winning golf courses. There's even a skate park for teens (or really cool adults). As a gorgeous summer getaway, Sun Valley is aptly named.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Poconos</location>
        <state>Pennsylvania</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Pennsylvania's Poconos deliver a great value for the adventure-bound traveler. Take your pick of 150 lakes, including gorgeous Lake Wallenpaupack, for endless water-borne recreation. Lace up your boots for some back country nature walking or gaze up at the stars as you roast marshmallows in a remote camp site. Tired of roughing it? Just check into one of the area's luxury resorts or B&Bs, situated mere feet from your next excursion.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Gatlinburg/Pigeon Forge</location>
        <state>North Carolina</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[America's most visited (and arguably most beautiful) national park, Great Smoky Mountains National Park spans some 800 square miles of protected forest along the border of North Carolina and Tennessee. Establish your base in friendly Gatlinburg, then explore the park's hundreds of trails by foot or horseback. From waterfalls to mountain peaks, the area's natural wonders guarantee repeat visits.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
            <row locid="180153" lat="35.996647" long="-112.099818">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Grand Canyon/Sedona</location>
        <state>Arizona</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwest Arizona]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[There's a reason why they don't call it "the sort of impressive canyon." Sedona, Arizona is the ideal spot to comprehend the scope and majesty of one of America's natural wonders. Start at Grand Canyon National Park where you can take it in at Pipe Creek Vista and Yavapai Point. Venture into relaxed Sedona, your base camp for treks among red rock monoliths named Coffeepot, Snoopy, and Cathedral. Here's where nature puts on a spectacular show.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="180673" lat="37.737269" long="-119.583218">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Yosemite</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Yosemite Falls is the world's 5th tallest waterfall]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[You've seen the Ansel Adams photographs, now experience Yosemite in full color. Trek by car or foot through this setting of peace and beauty formed by the violence of earthquakes and glaciers. Stargaze, kayak, fish, or cling to a sheer rock face. And be sure to experience the grandeur of Yosemite Falls, the world's 5th tallest waterfall. For families looking to escape to nature or couples looking for romance, Yosemite's beauty stirs the soul.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3846" lat="44.695912" long="-111.176156">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Yellowstone</location>
        <state>Montana</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Established in 1872]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[America's oldest national park, Yellowstone is still one of the best. Marvel at the world's most extraordinary geysers, hot springs, and geological wonders. Catch a glimpse of abundant native wildlife, including grizzlies, wolves, bison, and elk. Take a dip in a 50-yard-long band of thermal soaking pools along the Gardner River. Finally, make your trip truly memorable by visiting the majestic Grand Canyon of Yellowstone.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="500733" lat="43.485022" long="-110.780968">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Grand Tetons / Jackson Hole</location>
        <state>Wyoming</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Located in northwestern Wyoming]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Rising dramatically above placid alpine lakes, Wyoming's Grand Tetons lure travelers looking for rugged adventure or peaceful escape. Set up camp in Jackson, either at a campsite or an elegant yet rustic spa resort. Then take in the wonders of one of the world's most recognizable mountain landscapes by hiking or biking verdant trails. Bonus points for spotting celebrities - Jackson Hole valley is the weekend retreat for a number of famous faces.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="10150" lat="38.932373" long="-119.979255">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Lake Tahoe</location>
        <state>California</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Lake Tahoe Shakespeare Festival]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Think of skiing when you think of Lake Tahoe? Think again. This warm-weather getaway boasts 191 square miles of sparkling blue water ideal for summer recreation. Sail, hike, bike, or paddleboat, or head into town for an adventure in shopping and fine dining. Catch one of the area's legendary summer events - the Tahoe Shakespeare Festival, perchance? One of America's most beautiful places offers families and couples countless outdoor memories.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="9569" lat="43.647087" long="-89.768505">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Wisconsin Dells</location>
        <state>Wisconsin</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Waterpark Capital of the World!&#153;]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[There are so many attractions in Wisconsin's The Dells that it'll take more than one trip to experience them all. Kids will love getting soaked at the area's famous water parks - bring your trunks and see why The Dells is called the water park capital of the world. Travel by horse-drawn carriage through the magnificent cliff-walled gorges of Lost Canyon. Or take a drive then a dip into picturesque lakes on one of many amphibious vehicle tours.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="7612" lat="48.424923" long="-114.372314">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Glacier / Whitefish</location>
        <state>Montana</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Pristine forests, alpine meadows.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Glacier, Montana is a hiker's paradise with over 700 miles of trails, from scenic and leisurely to rugged and exhausting. Savor the solitude of a deep wilderness excursion or pack a picnic and take in the vistas in a flower-covered alpine meadow. Stop in nearby Whitefish for horseback rides and a stay in one of the town's many welcoming inns. When you travel to this beautiful part of Montana, be sure to bring your sense of wonder.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="996" lat="39.7934" long="-104.886891">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Denver</location>
        <state>Colorado</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Red Rocks Amphitheatre]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[With 205 parks in city limits and 20,000 acres of parks in the nearby mountains, the most difficult decision facing visitors to Denver, Colorado is whether to take in the scenery by bike or hiking boots. You don't even have to leave city limits to enjoy mountain biking - Denver cyclists brag about their 850 miles of paved, off-road trails. Want to experience the South Platte River? Do it with gusto on 17 miles of kayak chutes.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="6059168" lat="44.719488" long="-85.591775">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Traverse City</location>
        <state>Michigan</state>
        <site><![CDATA[ Sleeping Bear Sand Dunes]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The Tuscany-like countryside surrounding Traverse City produces grapes, meaning this Michigan locale is the heart of Midwestern wine country. After you've taken in the bucolic charms of the vineyards, head to over 180 miles of Lake Michigan shoreline for some sailing or sunbathing. Seeking more fun? Upscale golf courses and a historic downtown lined with shops make this an unforgettable getaway.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="460" lat="30.358724" long="-97.805189">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Austin</location>
        <state>Texas</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Enchanted Rock (TX state park).]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[You might know Austin, Texas for its abundant music and arts scene, but take a look at its natural wonders. Start with 785-foot Mount Bonnell, one of the city's most enduring attractions. Enjoy miles of trails in picnic-friendly McKinney Falls State Park, named after the spectacular waterfalls gracing its 635 acres. Then watch expert climbers defy gravity as they scale Enchanted Rock, rising high above the ruggedly beautiful landscape.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="retreats" reg="intl">
      <row locid="1222" lat="43.776459" long="11.250538">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Florence</location>
        <state>Italy</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Renaissance city of Florence.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Rekindle your romance in Tuscany, a region of central Italy rich with stunning, rural landscapes and vibrant artistic traditions. Bike through the vineyards and rolling hills of the Tuscan countryside, stopping for a sip at village cafes and wineries. Stroll the twisting streets of Florence, home of the Italian Renaissance, taking in art at the city's many galleries. Then cap the day at a candlelit table for two at a neighborhood bistro.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="2734" lat="48.851961" long="2.360312">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Paris</location>
        <state>France</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the Eiffel tower at sunset.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[There is no better destination for a romantic getaway than Paris. Tour the Eiffel Tower at sunset and watch the city come to life below. Pack a bottle of Bordeaux and a baguette for a picnic at the Ch&acirc;teau de Versaille, a 17th-century palace outside the city. Stroll the banks of the Seine, site of countless love scenes, both cinematic and genuine. And remember to walk the Champs Elysees, where lovely sidewalk cafes and local characters abound.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3687" lat="45.401659" long="12.350157">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Venice</location>
        <state>Italy</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Tour the venetian villas.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Venice is the city of canals, bridges, and serious romance. Climb aboard a gondola - those iconic vessels of Venetian lore - and take a ride down the Grand Canal. Relax at a canal-front caf&eacute; with a bottle of Chianti as musicians serendade from the water, or enjoy a leisurely stroll through cobbled alleys to the beautiful Bridge of Sighs. Finish your day with tiramisu and champagne at one of the city's many fine gourmet restaurants.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="935" lat="21.095766" long="-86.818376">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Riviera Maya</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Honeymooner's paradise.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Thanks to its many luxurious, couples-only resorts, the Riviera Maya has carved out a niche as a honeymooner's paradise. Treat yourselves to a champagne breakfast in bed, rose petals in your room, or a candlelit dinner in the shallows of a secluded pool. If you can imagine it, these resorts can make it happen. Should you find yourself newly engaged, you'll have no trouble planning the wedding: many properties offer wedding packages.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_summitco_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="60083" lat="45.596334" long="-73.624619">
        <region>North America</region>
        <location>Montreal</location>
        <state>Quebec</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Old Montreal]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Re-discover romance on the cobblestone streets of Old Montreal - the historical city center that's loaded with museums, shops, and restaurants. Embark on a 90-minute tour of the waterfront aboard the Parisian-style Bateau-Mouche, with views from La Ronde to the Olympic Stadium. Or take a romantic picnic to the Parc de la Promenade Bellerive, a 22-acre park on the banks of the St. Lawrence River.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="1553" lat="43.106606" long="-79.002055">
        <region>United States of America</region>
        <location>Niagara Falls</location>
        <state>New York</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Honeymoon Capital of the World]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[What is it about falling water that makes us fall in love? It's hard to say, but one thing is clear: Niagara Falls is a honeymooner's paradise. Today couples seeking a great value pick Niagara after they've tied the knot. Get up close to this cascading natural wonder by boat and enjoy a romantic evening light and fireworks show. And be sure to savor the offerings of area's many excellent restaurants and spas.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3704" lat="48.194099" long="16.390708">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Vienna</location>
        <state>Austria</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Capital of the Austro-Hungarian empire.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Romance echoes through Vienna's historical Innere Stadt. At sunset, stroll the Stephansplatz - the city's central square - and watch as the towering cathedral comes alive with lights. Score a table at the renowned Osterreicher Im Mak and linger over a Viennese meal of savory goulash, bread dumplings, and a bottle of Riesling. Looking for entertainment? Top off the evening at a performance of the Vienna State Opera, one of the world's finest.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>v
            </row>
      <row locid="2526" lat="43.688177" long="7.237287">
        <region>Europe</region>
        <location>Nice</location>
        <state>France</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Sweeping Mediterranean views.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Golden Mediterranean sunshine bathes the city of Nice, the unofficial capital of the Riviera. Spend a morning cycling through lavender fields outside the city. For lunch, break out a blanket, some brie, a baguette, and wine on the beach, then take an afternoon stroll down the cobbled streets of Old Town. Afterward, explore nearby Colline du Ch&acirc;teau ("Castle Hill"), a treasured park with fig trees and breathtaking views of the city below.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="3289" lat="18.347741" long="-64.917307">
        <region>Indonesia</region>
        <location>Kuta</location>
        <state>Bali</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Romantic getaway spot in Ubud.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Whatever your definition of romance, Bali has a setting for you. Go glitzy with a private beachfront villa at a luxury resort, where you'll dine at a candlelit table in the sand. If local culture is a priority, head to an elite hideaway in the mountain village of Ubud, an active hub of Balinese artisans. Or escape to the island's isolated southern beaches, where the crowds are appreciably smaller.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="279" lat="16.8155" long="-99.83271">
        <region>Mexico</region>
        <location>Acapulco</location>
        <state>Mexico</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Las Brisas Acapulco.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Acapulco's mix of high-end resorts and budget lodging make it an excellent choice for romantics from any tax bracket. Rekindle the fire at Las Brisas, with hilltop casitas, private plunge pools, and beachfront dining. Walk the shores of Acapulco Bay at sunset before ordering the fresh lobster at one of the city's finest restaurants. For a more affordable yet equally romantic getaway, hit up the oceanfront grills and palapas to the north of town.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="279" lat="16.8155" long="-99.83271">
        <region>Fiji</region>
        <location>Fiji</location>
        <state>Fiji</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Las Brisas Acapulco.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[Of the 332 islands that comprise the nation of Fiji, only 110 are inhabited. The country has a wealth of unspoiled tropical beaches, reefs, and islets. Island-hop in the exceptional Yasawa Group, a 12-island archipelago that's home to budget digs (i.e. thatched huts) and premier resorts (i.e. private cabanas with air conditioning and butler service). The islands are also have their share of adults-only resorts, all the better for a party of two.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
      <row locid="279" lat="16.8155" long="-99.83271">
        <region>French Polynesia</region>
        <location>French Polynesia</location>
        <state>French Polynesia</state>
        <site><![CDATA[Las Brisas Acapulco.]]></site>
        <description><![CDATA[The stunning Society Islands are the beating heart of French Polynesian culture and history. Here you'll discover the impossibly picturesque islands of Bora Bora and Tahiti. Snorkel in Bora Bora's crystal clear lagoon, picnic on a pristine white sand beach, or dine on authentic French cuisine at the elegant Villa Mahana. For dessert, simply stroll Le Marche - Tahiti's bustling market - while snacking on crêpes from a street cart.]]></description>
        <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
      </row>
    </destinations>
    <destinations category="retreats" reg="US">
        <row locid="3079" lat="32.090243" long="-81.164637">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Savannah</location>
            <state>Georgia</state>
            <site><![CDATA[A Savannah carriage ride.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Savannah, Georgia's classic Southern architecture, leafy boulevards, and cobblestone parks provide lucky visitors with an endlessly charming romantic backdrop. Stroll through meticulously maintained gardens in the city's Landmark Historical District. Explore galleries overflowing with the work of talented local artists, and dine at fine establishments where the waiter quickly becomes your new best friend. Savannah is a city to fall in love with.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3132" lat="37.75773" long="-122.446093">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>San Francisco</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Twin Peaks]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Famous for streetcars, fine cuisine, and charming boutique hotels, San Francisco is the romantic getaway of choice for those in love with beautiful cities. Experience the beauty of the Bay at Golden Gate Park. Explore crooked Lombard Street or North Beach cafes where poets moved their generations. Start the evening together by taking in the sunset from Twin Peaks or Coit Tower on Telegraph Hill. Let the City by the Bay take your breath away.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3121" lat="47.621862" long="-122.309731">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Seattle</location>
            <state>Washington</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Dinner, sights from atop the Space Needle.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[From the iconic Space Needle where diners marvel at mountain views, to the galleries and shops of historical Pioneer Square, Seattle, Washington welcomes visitors with an array of romantic enclaves. Take a sunset cruise on Elliott Bay or stroll among flowers and fruit at Pike Place Market. Whether you explore museums, fine dining, entertainment, or all the above, your visit to Seattle promises to be sleepless and memorable.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_crestedbutte_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="9019" lat="41.487635" long="-71.328414">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Newport</location>
            <state>Rhode Island</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Wine tasting at local vineyards, fine dining, spa.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Newport, Rhode Island was the vacation playground of choice for Gilded Age aristocrats, who constructed opulent mansions along the shore. Many of these manses are open to the public, welcoming travelers smitten with the romance of the past. Rent a sailboat for an afternoon, or luxuriate with a trip for two to the spa. At day's end, curl up with a glass of local wine at any of the town's premier dining destinations.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6141" lat="38.299299" long="-122.300639">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Napa</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Guided River Cruise on the Napa River.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Wine is only the beginning of a romantic getaway to Napa Valley. Enjoy a guided cruise on the Napa River, where local personalities help you spot wildlife along the banks while you enjoy a bottle of vino. Pack up your picnic and wind through the countryside by bicycle. With an abundance of spas, some of the finest dining this side of paradise, and gorgeous scenery, Napa Valley is a place where love blooms among the vines.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="6141" lat="38.299299" long="-122.300639">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>New York City</location>
            <state>New York</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Guided River Cruise on the Napa River.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[What's not to love about New York? The city of Woody Allen's romantic comedies, world-famous parks, and dining to die for makes romance not only possible, but inevitable. Start with a carriage ride around Central Park and stop off at any of the astounding museums that ring its perimeter. Bop along in a jazz club or experience the grandeur of the latest operatic masterpiece. Don't just enjoy a night out on the town, enjoy a night out on the town.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="10200" lat="29.923679" long="-81.413296">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>St. Augustine</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[St. Augustine is the nations oldest city filled with historic architecture.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the romance and beauty of America's oldest city, St. Augustine, Florida. Here you can tour the historical architecture from the comfort of trains, trolleys, or a horse-drawn carriage. Indulge in some retail therapy among many fine arts and crafts shops and savor an intimate fine dining experience. Conquistadors believed this to be the site of the Fountain of Youth, and after your refreshing visit, you may be inclined to agree.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3289" lat="18.347741" long="-64.917307">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>St. John</location>
            <state>U.S. Virgin Islands</state>
            <site><![CDATA[St. Croix is the largest of the United States Virgin Islands.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[A typical romantic night out for natives of the U.S. Virgin Islands includes a moon-lit walk on beach, a dinner of seafood caught just that afternoon, and cocktails quaffed to the beat of Calypso drummers. Why not go local? Explore secluded St. John, two-thirds of which is a lush national park. Stroll among the mills and sugarcane plantations of St. Croix. Or take a day trip by ferry to St. Thomas's pristine beaches. You won't want to leave...]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
    
    <destinations category="spas" reg="US">
        <row locid="9829" lat="33.587334" long="-111.857736">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Scottsdale</location>
            <state>Arizona</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Best resort spas in the country.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Some of the finest spa resorts in the country lie within reach of Phoenix, Arizona. These desert oases among cacti and magnificent rock formations offer services inspired by the natural elements. Take your pick from the endless variety of treatments, from Asian-inspired to Swedish to stress-eliminating hot stone massages. What could possibly add to the experience? World-class shopping and some of the finest cuisine in the Southwest.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_aspensnowmass_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2008" lat="36.129911" long="-115.124986">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Las Vegas</location>
            <state>Nevada</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Las Vegas features more than 30 spa facilities.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Step away from the energy of the gaming floor at many of Las Vegas's most popular casinos and you'll find a wealth of comforting spa getaways. With more than 30 facilities to choose from, you can explore a wide variety of treatments, from Shiatsu and Swedish massages to aromatherapy, herbal wraps, and reflexology. Having a girls' getaway? Sign up for manicures, pedicures, and facials. Or simply relax in a sauna and let your cares drift away.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_vail_bc_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3068" lat="35.743606" long="-106.013383">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Santa Fe</location>
            <state>New Mexico</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Swedish, Native American, and European Methods are used.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Santa Fe, New Mexico draws visitors passionate about the healing arts. Experience treatments inspired by Native American, Japanese, and European methods in several specialized spas. Your adventure into renewal and rejuvenation can include explorations into Chinese medicine, modern shamanism, astrology, hypnosis, or just tried-and-true Swedish massage. Best of all, you'll enjoy your spa experience in a city filled with art and natural beauty.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3068" lat="35.743606" long="-106.013383">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Oahu</location>
            <state>Hawaii</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Swedish, Native American, and European Methods are used.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Ancient Hawaiians believed in lokahi, the idea that all living things are connected. This spirit suffuses the many spa resorts concentrated in Waikiki. Find your center in a yoga or tai chi session on the beach or a lush, tropical garden. Bathe in the kawehewehe, or "healing waters" of Gray's Beach. And don't forget there's nothing quite as refreshing as a walk on one of Oahu's legendary shorelines at sunrise or sunset.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3068" lat="35.743606" long="-106.013383">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Kauai</location>
            <state>Hawaii</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Swedish, Native American, and European Methods are used.]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[When you partake in an outdoor spa treatment in the calming breezes of Kauai, you're participating in ancient Hawaiian healing practices. Here you'll find deep calm on the beach or beside the sacred Wailua River. You'll experience Lomi Lomi massage, based on the Polynesian idea of <em>huna</em>, meaning "everything seeks love." Beginning with a traditional Hawaiian blessing, this treatment is just the first step in your peaceful journey.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_steamboat_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="2885" lat="33.843378" long="-116.539483">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Palm Springs</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[MiraMonte Resort and Spa]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Palm Springs is the traditional getaway for Hollywood celebs seeking a quiet place to refocus their creative energies. Rediscover your own inner peace with hydrotherapy or enjoy an abundance of skin treatments designed to keep you beautiful. Take refuge in a boutique resort spa, or bring your friends along to one of the area's hip and swanky day spas. After a day of pampering, delicious food, and deep relaxation, you'll feel like a movie star.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_telluride_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="9061" lat="26.66547" long="-80.038368">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Palm Beach</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[The Best of Everything]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Among spa aficionados, Palm Beach is known to have "the best of everything." A variety of full-service facilities employ some of the most talented practitioners of European massage techniques you're likely to find. Refocus in spas rated in the top ten by Zagat. Slip into the "Waters of the World," a series of outdoor pools infused with salts and minerals imported from the Dead Sea and French Pyrenees. Afterward, world-class golf and dining await.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_winterpark_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="3081" lat="34.431113" long="-119.733437">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Santa Barbara</location>
            <state>California</state>
            <site><![CDATA[The Four Seasons Resort, Biltmore Hotel]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Seaside luxury beckons travelers to Santa Barbara, California. Enjoy some of the highest of high-end resorts as well as bargains on treatments at rejuvenating day spas. Embark on a wine-tasting tour arranged by your concierge or relax after a day on the golf course with a shiatsu massage. Or simply breathe the salty breeze along some of the area's most beguiling coastline. Santa Barbara provides pleasure in its many forms.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/Dest_Whistler_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="1000" lat="32.787776" long="-96.786675">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Dallas</location>
            <state>Texas</state>
            <site><![CDATA[Complete with world-class facilities]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Those seeking the fulfillment of a healing spa experience need look no further than Dallas, Texas. Luxuriate in mud and salt treatments, herbal wraps, and aromatherapy massage at four- and five-star resorts. Start your day with pilates, yoga, or tai chi, then break for a healthy spa cuisine lunch. Traveling with a friend? Try side by side shiatsu massage. And if golf's your game, you'll find the city's sculpted courses world-class.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_banff_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
        <row locid="401" lat="26.144156" long="-81.690711">
            <region>United States of America</region>
            <location>Naples</location>
            <state>Florida</state>
            <site><![CDATA[World class golf resorts]]></site>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover intimate spas and stunningly beautiful resorts in sun-blessed Naples, Florida. It's a calming place to try new and wondrous methods of relaxation. How about a honeysuckle scrub or frangipani wrap? Let serenity be your guide as you work on the perfect Florida tan or hydrate your skin with a fresh sugarcane treatment. Once you're reinvigorated, hit the courts for some tennis or inhale gentle ocean breezes on a secluded stretch of beach.]]></description>
            <image>http://media.expedia.com/media/content/expus/graphics/storefronts/ski/dest_saltlake_124x89.gif</image>
        </row>
    </destinations>
  </destinationpages>
  
  <categoryfinder>
    <location name="Anaheim">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Asheville">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Aspen">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Atlanta">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Atlantic City">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Austin">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Big Island">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Big Sky">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Biloxi">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Boise">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Boston">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Cape Cod">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Charleston, SC">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Chicago">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Clearwater - St Petersburg">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Dallas">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Denver">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Denver-Boulder">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Detroit">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Fort Lauderdale">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Ft Myers">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Gatlinburg - Pigeon">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Glacier - Whitefish">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Grand Canyon - Sedona">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Grand Tetons - Jackson Hole">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Houston">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Kauai">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Lake Tahoe">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Las Vegas">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Laughlin">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Los Angeles">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Mackinac Island">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Maui">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Miami">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Minneapolis-St. Paul">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Monterey">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Myrtle Beach">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Naples">
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="12">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Nashville">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="New Orleans">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="New York">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Newport">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Oahu">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Orange County">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Orlando">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Palm Beach">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Palm Springs">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Park City">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Petoskey, MI">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="5">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Philadelphia">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Phoenix">
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Pigeon Forge">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Poconos">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Portland">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Providence">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Puerto Rico">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Reno">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Salt Lake City">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="San Antonio">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="San Diego">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="US" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="San Francisco">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sandusky">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Santa Barbara">
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Santa Fe">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Savannah">
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Scottsdale">
      <category cat="spas" reg="US" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Seaside, OR">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Seattle">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Shrevport">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Snowmass-Aspen">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="South Padre">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="South Tahoe">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="US" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="St. Augustine">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Stowe">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sun River - Bend">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sun Valley">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Tampa">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="The Dells">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="USVI">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="USVI - St. Thomas">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Vail">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Virginia Beach">
      <category cat="escapes" reg="US" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Washington DC">
      <category cat="cities" reg="US" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Williamsburg">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="US" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Wine Country">
      <category cat="dining" reg="US" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="US" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Wisconsin Dells">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="US" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Yellowstone">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Yosemite">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="US" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Acapulco">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Andalucia, Spain">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Anguilla">
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Antigua">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Aruba">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Athens">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Auckland New Zealand">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Austria">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Baden (Germany)">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Bahamas">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Bali">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Banff-Jasper">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Bangkok">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Barbados">
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Barcelona">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Beijing">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Bermuda">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Biarritz">
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Buenos Aires">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Calgary">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Cancun">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Copehagen">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Costa Rica">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Cozumel">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Dominican Republic">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Dubai">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Edmonton">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Fiji">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Florence">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="French Alps">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="French Polynesia">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Greek Islands">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Hong Kong">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Istanbul">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Jamaica">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Jasper National Park, Alberta">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Jerusalem">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Kerry, Ireland">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Lake Como">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Lake Louise-Banff">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Lake Maggiore">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Lima, Peru">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="London">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Los Cabos">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Macau">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Madrid">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Melbourne">
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Mexico City">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Mont Tremblant">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Monte Carlo">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Montreal">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Moscow">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="N. Italy - Dolomites">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Niagara Falls">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Nice">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Okanagan Valley, BC">
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Osaka">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Oslo, Norway">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Panorama, BC">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Paris">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Phuket-Ko Samui">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Prague">
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Puerto Vallarta">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Rio de Janeiro">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Riviera Maya">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Rome">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
      <category cat="historical" reg="intl" friendly="8">Historical and Cultural experiences</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Salzburg, Austria">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sao Paulo">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Scotland">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="St. Lucia">
      <category cat="" reg="" friendly="">All-Inclusive Hotspots</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="St. Martin-St. Maarten">
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sun Peaks, BC">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Surrey, England">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sweden">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Swiss Alps">
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Sydney">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Tokyo">
      <category cat="familyfun" reg="intl" friendly="2">Amusement-Theme Parks</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Toronto">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Utrecht (Netherlands)">
      <category cat="casinos" reg="intl" friendly="5">Casinos Galore</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Vallarta">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Vancouver">
      <category cat="cities" reg="intl" friendly="4">Bright Lights, Big Cities</category>
      <category cat="dining" reg="intl" friendly="6">Food and Wine - Culinary Adventures</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Venice">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Victoria, BC">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="3">Beach and Island Escapes</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Vienna">
      <category cat="retreats" reg="intl" friendly="12">Romantic Retreats</category>
    </location>
    <location name="Whistler">
      <category cat="golf" reg="intl" friendly="7">Golf Getaways</category>
      <category cat="outdoors" reg="intl" friendly="8">Outdoors</category>
      <category cat="spas" reg="intl" friendly="11">Resort and Spa Locales</category>
    </location>
  </categoryfinder>
  <soatripfinder>
    <region id="9173">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">115</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">499</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="6004910">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">88</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">378</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="3132">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">215</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">599</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="1503">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">788</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">400</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="6895">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">315</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">799</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="2434">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">889</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">325</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="10322">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">415</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">200</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="9169">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">550</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">425</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="6141">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">415</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">600</pkgprice>
    </region>
    <region id="2759">
      <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">300</hotelprice>
      <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">800</pkgprice>
    </region>
      <region id="3687">
          <hotelprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">672</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice url="http://www.expedia.com/">1804</pkgprice>
      </region>

      <region id="178229" name="Amsterdam">
          <hotelprice>88.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1222.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178232" name="Atlanta">
          <hotelprice>117.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>567.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178233" name="Auckland">
          <hotelprice>108.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1451.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178235" name="Baltimore">
          <hotelprice>174.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>490.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178236" name="Bangkok">
          <hotelprice>49.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1365.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178237" name="Beijing">
          <hotelprice>64.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1494.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178239" name="Boston">
          <hotelprice>80.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>421.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178242" name="Buenos Aires">
          <hotelprice>97.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1193.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178245" name="Calgary">
          <hotelprice>75.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>577.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="178318" name="Washington DC" />
      <region id="179991" name="Acapulco">
          <hotelprice>49.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>516.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="179995" name="Cancun">
          <hotelprice>60.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>0.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="180390" name="Barbados">
          <hotelprice>66.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>0.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="601713" name="Aruba">
          <hotelprice>95.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>605.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="601784" name="Bahamas">
          <hotelprice>172.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>715.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="602291" name="Banff/Lake Louise">
          <hotelprice>153.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>691.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="602484" name="Bahamas">
          <hotelprice>210.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>824.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="6046791" name="Antalya">
          <hotelprice>61.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1705.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      <region id="6053838" name="Abu Dhabi">
          <hotelprice>150.0000</hotelprice>
          <pkgprice>1903.0000</pkgprice>
      </region>
      
  </soatripfinder>
</tripfinder>